ok商店QQ：2875745612
ok商店博客:blog.ok68.eu.org
章節一 去紅石鎮的最後一輛車
Chapter One Last Stage to Red Rock
還有位置坐個人不
Got room for one more?
你他媽是誰 他們是怎麼回事
Who the hell are you, and what happened to them?
沃倫·馬奎斯少校前美國騎兵
Names Major Marquis Warren former U.S. Cavalry.
現在是法院的僱員
Currentrly I'm a servant of the court.
抓一些壞人去交易
Tryin' to bringin' a coupla' no-goods into market.
我口袋裏有關於他們的文件
I got paperwork on 'em in my pocket.
你抓他們去紅石鎮
You takin' 'em into Red Rock?
我覺得你也想去那 是吧
I figure that's where you headed, right?
我這一路上過來 無休止的暴風雪在我身後下了三小時了
That damblasted blizzards been on our ass for the last three hours.
我們估計沒可能在它趕上咱們之前到達紅石鎮了
Ain't no way we gonna make it all the way to Red Rock 'fore it catches us.
所以你是趕著去明妮的男裝店
So ya' hightailin' it halfway to Minnie's Haberdashery?
對的
You know I am.
我能上車不 等等 煙鬼
- May I come aboard? - Well smoke...
上不上得我決定
it up to me, yes.
但是也不由我決定 那由誰決定
- But it ain't up to me. - Who's it up to?
馬車裏的這傢伙說了算
Fella in the wagon.
馬車裏的傢伙對多個人沒意見吧
Fella' in the wagon not partial to company?
那人他為了自己的私人旅途付了錢 我只是想告訴你
Fella' in the wagon he paid for a private trip. And i'm here to tell ya'...
他為了隱私付了好多錢 所以你要是想跟我們一起去明妮那咯
he paid a pretty penny for privacy. So if you wanna' go to Minnie's with us...
你得跟他說去 好吧
- you gotta' talk to him. - Well...
我這不去了嘛
that's what i'll do.
等等 黑夥計
Hold it black fella'!
你靠近之前
'fore you approach,
你帶上你的兩把槍 然後把它們放在那邊石頭上
you take them two guns of yours and lay 'em on that rock over yonder.
把雙手舉過你的帽子
Then you raise both your hands way above your hat.
再靠近
Then you approach...
像黑糖黏住般緩慢地過來
molasses-like.
真夠相信人的 是吧
Real trustin' fella', huh?
沒那麼相信
Not so much.
把槍放下吧
Put 'em down.
走過來
Come on ahead.
他媽的 我說了把手舉過你的帽子
I said way above your hat, god dammit.
現在上前來吧
Now come forward.
這樣差不多遠了
That's far enough.
我會很固執的 我認識你 黑夥計
I'll be dogged, you black fella' i know.
行了 叫沃倫什麼 對吧
Col. Something Warren, right?
沃倫·馬奎斯少校
Major Marquis Warren.
我也認識你
I know you too.
我們曾經在（田納西州）查塔努加 一起吃過牛排
We shared a steak dinner once upon a time in Chattanooga.
絞刑者 魯斯·約翰
You John Ruth, The Hangman.
是我是我
That be me.
都過去多久了 上次吃牛排至今
- How longs that been? - Since that steak?
八個月了
Eight months.
所以你跟我解釋一下
So why don't you explain to me...
一個非洲裔賞金獵人在下著大雪的
what an african bounty hunter's doin' wanderin'
懷俄明州中部瞎逛什麼
around in the snow in the middle of Wyoming.
我正嘗試帶一些有賞金的人去紅石鎮
I'm tryin' to get a coupla' of bounty's to Red Rock.
所以你還在幹活咯
So you still in business?
你知道的
You know I am.
你的馬怎麼了
What happened to your horse?
環境導致我們走這麼久的路途 我的馬估計到不了
Circumstances caused us to take the long way around. My horse couldn't make it.
你認不認識這個騎馬的人
You don't know nothin' about this fella here?
不認識
Nope.
他連你什麼名字都不知道
Don't even know your name?
不知道
Nope.
好吧 我覺得這是個巧合
Well I guess that makes this one fortuitous wagon.
我他媽也是這麼覺得的
I sure as hell hope so.
沃倫·馬奎斯少校這是 多茉歌·黛西
Major Marquis Warren, this here is Daisy Domergue.
多茉歌 這是 沃倫少校
Domergue, to you, this is Major. Warren.
咋地了 黑鬼
Howdy nigger!
她脾氣挺爆的 是吧
She's a pepper, ain't she?
小姑娘 你不知道 深色皮膚的人不喜歡
Now girl, don't you know darkee's don't like bein'
再被叫 黑鬼 他們覺得很無禮
called niggers no more. They find it offensive.
我有叫得更難聽過我信我信
- I been called worse. - Now that I can believe.
聽說過她不 我應該麼
- Heard of her? - Should I?
她雖然不是 （刺殺林肯的兇手）布思 但是
Well she ain't no John Wilkes Booth, but...
也許你聽說過關於取她首級的價格
maybe you might of heard tell 'bout the price on her head.
多少 一萬美元
- How much? - Ten thousand dollars.
媽蛋 她幹嘛了 殺了 藍趣·莉莉
Damn, what she do? Kill Lily Langtree?
沒有沒有
Not quite.
現在一萬塊已經基本上在我口袋了
Now that ten thousand's practically in my pocket.
所以我才不想跟別人一起坐
It's why I ain't too anxious to be handin' out rides.
特別是為了賺錢的職業殺手
Especially to professionals open for business.
好吧 我完全能理解 我對她一點想法都沒有
Well I certainly can appreciate that. I ain't got no designs on her.
我那邊的一個哥們值四千
One of my fella's over there is worth four
一個值三千 一個值一千
thousand, one's worth three, and one's worth one.
我確定對我來說已經夠不錯了
That's damn sure good enough for me.
好吧
Well...
讓我看看他們的通緝令
Let me see their paperwork.
跟我之前說的 像黑糖黏住般慢慢的
Like I said, molasses-like.
退後點
Back off.
嘿
Look...
我實在是不想打斷你們 但這正下暴風雪呢
I sure hate to interrupt y'all! But we gtta' cold damn blizzard,
我們得趕緊找個地方躲躲
hot on our asses we tryin' to beat to shelter!
我明白
I realize that!
在我思考的這時候 你給我趕緊閉嘴 抓緊那些馬
Now shut your mouth and hold them damn horses while I think!
好了 小伙子 我試試吧
Okay boy, we'll give it a try.
但你得把手槍放騎馬大哥那
But you leave those pistols over yonder with the driver.
你不會真讓那黑鬼上來吧
You ain't really gonna' let that nigger ridin' in
也許到那邊跟那個不認識的人（騎馬車的哥們） 但
here is ya'? I mean maybe up there with O.B., but-
被打的感覺怎麼樣 婊子
How you like the sound of them bells, bitch?
很爽 是吧
They are real pretty, ain't they?
你要是再張嘴說話
You open up your trashy mouth again, I'll knock
我就用槍把你牙都打掉 明白沒
out them front teeth for ya'. You got it?
嗯
Yeah.
我要聽你說 "我明白了"
Let me hear you say: "I got it."
我明白了
I got it.
我需要幫我把那幾個人放車頂上去
Well, I'm gonna need some help tyin' these fella's up on the roof.
等你到紅石鎮你給那哥們50塊 他會幫你的
Give O.B. fifty dollars when ya' get to Red Rock, and he'll help ya'.
好吧 我同意騎馬車的哥們 這暴風雪讓我很愁啊
Well, I agree with O.B. This storm's got me concerned.
你幫忙的話 我們能快點走
We get goin' a lot quicker you help out too.
媽個雞 我已經後悔同意你上車了
Goddamit to hell, I'm already regretting this!
我手跟她手銬一起呢 現在可幫不了你綁他們幾個
Now I can't likely help ya' tie fella's to the roof with my wrist cuffed to hers.
我手腕就一直銬著了
And my wrist is gonna' stay cuffed to hers, and
她是不會離開我半步的
she ain't never gonna' leave my goddamn side,
直到我把她送到紅石鎮監獄懂沒
until I personally put her in the Red Rock jail! Now do you got that?
好吧 我懂了非常好
- Yeah, I got it. - Good.
你馬是怎麼了
So what happend to your horse?
它老了
He got old.
我擁有它有一段時間了
I done had him for a bit.
天氣變得辣麼壞的時候
When the weather took a turn for the worse, he
它盡力了 然而並沒有什麼卵用
done what he could, but he couldn't make it.
太可惜了確實
- That's too bad. - Yes it is.
我和我的老馬一起騎了挺遠的了
Me an' ole Lash rode a lotta' miles together.
如果我把算傻逼動物看作朋友的話
You could say he was my best friend- if I
它可以算是我的老朋友了 然而我並不會
considered stupid animals firends, which I don't.
儘管我會想念它們的
Never the less... I'm gonna' miss 'em.
誰是 多茉歌·黛西
Who's Daisy Domergue?
就是一個 不是很屌的殺人犯婊砸
A no damn good murdering bitch, that's who.
我能看出來你把一個女人帶去絞刑 內心還挺淡定的
I can see you ain't got mixed emotions 'bout bringing a woman to a rope.
如果是女的 你在說她
- If by woman, you mean her?
不 內心一點都不會難過
No I do not have mixed emotions.
所以你是要帶她去紅石鎮吊起來咯
So you takin' her into Red Rock to hang?
不然呢 你要等著看吶
- You bet. - Gonna' wait to watch it?
那是當然
You know I am.
我想親耳聽見她背卡嚓斷掉的聲音
I wanna' hear her neck snap with my own two ears.
你從來不等他們絞刑
You never wait to watch 'em hang?
我的懸賞犯 從來不會被絞刑
My bounties never hang,
因為我從來不會活著帶他們去
cause I never bring 'em in alive.
從不
Never?
從來沒有
Never ever.
我們在查塔努加 說過這事
We talked about this in Chattanooga.
帶孤注一擲的的活人等於是自尋死路
Bringing desperate men in alive, is a good way to get yourself dead.
要是不閉眼 我會睡不著
Can't catch me sleepin' if I don't close my eyes.
我不想那麼敬業
I don't wanna' work that hard.
沒人說過這一行會很簡單
No one said the job was suppose to be easy.
同樣也沒人說過幹這一行會很辛苦
No one said it was suppose to be that hard, nether.
但那個小姑娘
But that little lady,
才是別人叫他 "絞刑者" 的原因
is why they call him "The Hangman".
懸賞令上寫的不論死活 所以其他人
When the handbill says Dead or Alive, the rest of
都會從高處就開槍從後背打你
us shoot ya' in the back from up on top of a perch
把你放到馬鞍上 但如果被魯斯·約翰這個絞刑者 抓住了
somewhere, bring ya' in dead over a saddle. But when John Ruth The Hangman catches ya',
你不會被子彈打死
you don't die by a bullet in the back.
當被絞刑者抓住了你只能被絞死
When The Hangman catches you... you hang.
你高估他們啦 哥們
You overrate 'em nigger.
我承認他很有膽量
I'll give you he got guts.
但是拼頭腦的話
But in the brains department,
他就像在淺水井裏要潛水的傻子
he like a man who took a high dive in a low well.
哈哈哈 好了 黛西
Now Daisy,
我希望你能理解一下 聊天信號
I want us to work out a signal system of communication.
當我非常狠地肘擊你臉的時候
When I elbow you real hard in the face...
意思是 閉嘴
that means: Shut up.
明白沒
You got it?
知道了
I got it.
我
I...
我知道我們之前只見過一面
I know we only met each other once before.
我不想過分表現得近乎 但
And I don't mean to unduly imply intimacy. But...
嗯
Well...
你還放著不
You still got it?
我還放著啥
I still got, what?
林肯的信
The Lincoln letter?
當然
Of course.
你放身上沒
Do you got it on you?
在哪
Where?
這呢
Right here.
我知道你對它非常小心
Look, I know you gotta' be real careful with it and all.
我能想像你不想
I can imagine you probably don't like to take
把它們經常從信封裏拿出來
it in an'out of the envelope all that often.
但是如果你不介意的話
But if you wouldn't mind,
我十分想再看一次
i'd sure appreciate seein' that again.
確實
You right,
我不是很喜歡經常拿出來看
I don't like taking it in an'out of the envelope that much.
是是是但是
- Yeah. - But...
看在你救我一命的份上
as your saving my life an' all,
我覺得我還是能讓你再看一遍的
I suppose I could let you read it again.
瑪麗·陶德來催我了 看來該睡覺了
"Ole Mary Todd's callin', so I guess it must be time for bed"
瑪麗·陶德
Ole Mary Todd.
真讓我不爽
That gets me.
我也不爽
That gets me too.
窮逼 你知道不?
You know what this is, tramp?
這是林肯的信
It's a letter from Lincoln.
林肯給他的信
It's a letter from Lincoln to him.
他們打仗的時候還通信
They shared a correspondence during the war.
他們是筆友 這還只是其中一封
They was pen pals. This is just one of the letters.
臥槽
What the...
馬伕
O.B.
停車
Stop!
放輕鬆 嘿
Whoa, easy.
這傻逼東西
Of all the stupid,
都要把我手臂撕下來了
like to rip my goddamn arm off!
我不是
I didn't,
拖她上山
drag her stikin' ass up this goddamn mountain, just
為了讓你在郊外打斷她脖子的
for you to break her neck on the ouskirts of town.
是你他媽的要把信給她的
You the one handed her my goddamn letter.
我沒給她 我給的是你
I didn't give it to her, I gave it to you!
那黑鬼想摔斷我舌頭
That nigger like to bust my jaw.
你把他信毀了
You ruin that letter of his,
那黑鬼不把你跺死 當他跺你的時候
that niggers gonna' stomp your ass to death. And when he do,
我就坐在馬車上邊看邊笑
I'm gonna sit back on that wagon wheel watch and laugh.
怎麼樣
How is it?
她一點用都沒的
She didn't help it none.
不過還好啦
But it's alright.
這就是你們黑鬼對女人的咯
Is that the way niggers treat their ladies?
你他媽的哪是女人
You... ain't no goddamn... lady!
嘿 魯斯先生
Hey Mister Ruth?
咋了
What?
那邊還有一個哥們走過來
There's another fella' on foot, up here on the road!
神馬
What?
我說 那邊有個哥們正走路過來
I said, there's another fella' on foot, up here on the road!
考慮到這正下著大暴雪
Considering there's a blizzard goin' on,
這麼多人在走來走去的 怎麼說 少校
whole lotta' fellas walkin' around, wouldn't you say, Major?
鑒於我是其中之一 嗯
Considerin I'm one half of them fellas, yeah...
應該會有挺多人
seems to be a lot of 'em.
那就不一樣了小伙子
This changes things, son.
八千塊對一個黑鬼來說是很多錢了
Eight thousand dollars a lotta' money for a nigger.
但有個同夥的話 一萬八確實是更好
But with a partner, eighteen's a whole lot better.
你真的以為我跟那個哥們是一夥的 或者跟那個女的
You really think I'm in cahoots wit' that fella'? Or her?
戴上它 我才不會戴手銬呢
- Put them on. - I ain't wearin' handcuffs.
你把手銬戴上 你就不用再擔心我開槍了
You put those on or you can stop worryin' about this whole thing, right now.
章節二倆大兄弟
Chapter Two Son of a Gun
把你武器交給馬伕
Hand your weapons to the driver.
太緊張吧你
Little jumpy, ain't you?
管他呢 照做就好了
Never mind the jokes, just do it.
你說了算 確實是
- If you say so. - I do.
好吧
Okay...
我交完了
I done did it.
馬伕 你拿到了
O.B.? Ya' got 'em?
拿著呢 好了 哥們
- I got 'em! - Okay fella',
你繼續用那隻手拿著燈籠
you keep holdin' that lantern in that one hand,
另一隻手放在我能看見的地方
and you keep that other hand where I can see it.
走過去 讓我好好看看你
Walk over there where I can get a good look at cha'.
我真是養了條好狗
I'll be a goddamn dog in the manger.
曼尼克斯·克裏斯 是你不
Is that you Chris Mannix?
不好意思 哥們 我們認識麼 不是很熟
- I'm sorry friend, do we know each other? - Not quite.
你認識這哥們不 就聽說過
- You know this fella'? - Only by reputation.
我剛才說了
Like I said friend,
你讓我有點小不利啊
you got me at a bit of a disadvantage.
讓你一直處於不利 我才能保持有利姿態啊
Keepin' you at a disadvantage, is a advantage I intend to keep.
先生不管你是誰
Whoever you are mister,
當你跟一個跪在雪中絕望的人聊天時 你聽上去確實挺耿直的
you sure sound tough when you're talkin' to a desperate man knee deep in snow.
我不想惹麻煩
I don't want no trouble.
我只是想搭個車 我快凍死了
I just wanna' ride. I'm freezin to death.
這傻逼是誰
Who is this joker.
你聽說過反叛者曼尼克斯·厄斯金 不
You heard of the rebel renegade Erskine Mannix?
曼尼克斯掠奪者 就是他們
- Mannix's Marauders? - That's them.
南加州的災難 曼尼克斯掠奪者
The scourge of South Carolina, Mannix Marauders.
那是他們中最小的那個 克裏斯
That's Erskine's youngest boy, Chris.
誰帶你來這條路的 曼尼克斯·克裏斯
What brings you in my path, Chris Mannix?
嗯 菲斯先生
Well Mr. Face,
我本來騎馬去紅石鎮的 結果我馬踩到雪裏的鼠洞了
I was riding to Red Rock and my horse stepped in a gopher hole in the snow,
弄壞了它的腿 不得不蹲著
fucked up his leg, an' had to put 'er down.
你去紅石鎮接單
You got business in Red Rock?
是啊 啥單子
- Yes I do. - What?
我是新的治安官
I'm the new sheriff.
狗屁 真事
- Horseshit. - 'fraid not.
你的星標呢 我還沒上任呢
- Where is your star? - Well I ain't the sheriff yet.
只要我一到他們答應讓我去的那裏 只是還沒到啊
Once I get there they swear me in, but that ain't happened yet.
我到那才能領到星標
And that's when you get your star.
你有證據證明這一切麼
You got anything that can back any of this up?
有 只要我們到紅石鎮
Yeah. When we get to Red Rock.
從那三個凍成傻逼的人的臉看來
And from the look of those three frozen fuckers up there,
你是個接單的賞金獵人啊
I figure you're a bounty hunter open for business.
我猜你帶這三個死人去紅石鎮領賞金吧
And I figure you're taking them three dead bodies into Red Rock to get paid?
三個死的
Three dead.
一個活的
One alive.
那是誰 多茉歌·黛西
- Who's that? - Daisy Domergue.
多茉歌·黛西是他媽的誰
Who the fuck is Daisy Domergue?
對於除了我和絞刑官的人來說 根本就不是什麼人
Not a goddamn thing to nobody, except me and the hangman.
絞刑者
The Hangman?
那我是更要他媽瘋了.
Well I'll be double dogged damned.
你就是絞刑者啊 魯斯·鮑勃是約翰
- You're The Hangman, Bob Ruth. - It's John.
你是
And you...
你是帶頭黑鬼
your're the nigger with the head...
馬庫斯少校
Major Marquis.
媽蛋 真的是馬庫斯少校在看我啊
My lord, is that really the real head of Major Marquis, lookin' at me now?
真的是我 還有我的頭
Yeah it's really me and it's really my head.
怎麼了哥們 你們倆在辦賞金獵人野餐啊
What's goin' on, y'all havin' a bounty hunters picnic?
無所謂了 你帶那三個死屍
Never mind, you takin' in them three dead bodies
還有她去紅石鎮去領賞金 是吧
and her to Red Rock to get paid, ain't ya'?
嗯
Yeah.
好吧
Well...
你們在紅石鎮領賞金的人就是我--新的治安官
the man is red Rock suppose to pay you is me. The new sherrif.
所以如果你想拿錢 你得帶我去紅石鎮
So if you wanna get paid, you need to get me to Red Rock.
不好意思 我是不太敢相信
Well execuse me for findin' it hard to belive a
你除了能去死以外 鎮選舉會讓你做什麼
town electin' you to do anything except drop dead.
所以我就應該凍死 因為你不相信某些事
So I'm suppose to freeze death, 'cause you find something hard to belive?
我想想還是算了
No I suppose not.
戴上它 再進來
Put them on and come inside.
不
No.
那你就凍去吧 那你就只能絞死那女的了
- Then you'll freeze. - Then you'll hang.
又怎樣
How so?
堅持住 馬伕
Stay strong Driver!
你能下來聊聊不
Could you come down here and join us?
我必須抓住這些馬 我在上面聽你們撕逼就剛剛好
I gotta hold these horses I can hear you just fine from up here.
你是不是聽見我告訴他 我是紅石鎮新來的治安官了
You heard me tell this fella' I'm the new sheriff of Red Rock, right?
是
Yeah.
紅石鎮是我的鎮子
Red Rock is my town.
我進我自己的小鎮還得戴著賞金獵人的手銬 不可能
And I'm gonna' enter my town in bounty hunters chains? No Sir!
不好意思 哥們 我才不會那樣進我的小鎮呢
Sorry bushwackers, I ain't entering Red Rock that way.
當你到紅石鎮之後 你就會明白
When you finally get to Red Rock, you're going
我說的每一件事 都他媽是對的
to realize every goddamn thing I said was right.
我指望你 馬伕
And I expect you, O.B.,
去告訴紅石鎮鎮民們
to tell the townsfolk of Red Rock that John
魯斯·約翰 把他們的治安官凍死了
Ruth, let their new sheriff freeze to death.
隊員們我的頭可不值錢
There ain't no bounty on my head, bushwacker.
你弄死我那可是謀殺
You let me die, that's murder.
伸出手來
Hold out your hands.
馬伕
O.B.
讓少校拿回他的槍
Give the Major back his iron.
有一件事我倒是確定了
One thing I know for sure,
這他媽的黑鬼跟你不是一夥的
this nigger-hatin' son of a gun ain't partnered up with you.
現在
Now...
我會幫你保護你的八千
I'll help protect your eight thousand,
你要幫我保護我的一萬
you help me protect my ten,
行不
deal?
愛是不是偉大 你們是不是要一起躺在地上做成個雪人啊
Ain't love grand. Y'all wanna' lie on the ground and make snow angels together?
鮑勃 我告訴你 我名字是 約翰
- Tell ya' what, Bob- - The name's John.
等我們到紅石鎮 我會請你們吃飯喝酒的
When we get to Red Rock, I'll buy you and Major Marquis there dinner and booze.
以作感謝 我不和
- May way of sayin' thanks. - I don't drink,
反叛者喝酒我確定我是不會和他們一起吃飯的
with rebel renegades, and I damn sure don't break bread with 'em.
好吧 魯斯
Well Mr. Ruth,
你聽上去要挺針對我們的事業啊
you sound like you got a axe to grind against The Cause.
你們那些反叛者的事業
The cause of a renegade army?
一群本地的垃圾我就是針對你們
A bunch of losers gone loco, you bet I do.
你們用反叛旗包裝自己 當做借口來偷蒙拐騙 殺人劫財
Ya' wrapped yourselves up in the Rebel Flag as an excuse to kill and steal.
沃倫 你應該會感興趣的 特別是對自由的黑人來說
And this should interest you Warren, in particular emancipated blacks.
聽上去像我的作風
Sounds like my kinda' fella'.
對我來說 你一定看了很多華盛頓DC 印刷的報紙
Sounds to me you been readin' a lotta' newspapers printed in Washington D.C.
無論如何 我只想讓你知道我很感激
Anywho, I'm just tryin' to let y'all know grateful I am.
我曾是將死之人 而你們救了我
I was a goner, and y'all saved me.
你要是真想感激的話
You wanna' show me how grateful you are...
那就閉嘴
shut up!
媽蛋 黛西 來了來了
God damnit, Daisy it's comin'.
給最後一片了
Here, last piece.
他知道你曾經有多出名不
Does he know how famous you once was?
我覺得不知道
I don't think so.
黑眼睛的
Black eye.
你知道他是誰不
Do you know who he is?
你問我知道不知道 政府在他身上
Do I know about the thirty thousand dollar reward
懸賞了三萬塊的 馬奎斯少校
the Confederacy put on the head of Major Marquis?
是啊
Yeah.
那些鄉巴佬們都在追殺這黑人的腦袋
Them hillbillies went nigger head hunting,
但是他們都沒殺到對的人 是吧
but they never did get 'em the right nigger head, did they?
是的 沒殺到
No they didn't.
但是從不缺少躍躍欲試者
But it wasn't for lack of tryin'.
那些像啄木鳥般的傢伙 收拾行李來到這下雪的山裏
Them peckawoods left their homes and their families, and come to this snowy mountain,
來尋找寶藏和我
lookin' for me and fortune.
並沒有人找到寶藏
None of them found fortune.
有幾個你從沒聽說過的人
The ones you ain't ever heard of no more,
他們發現了我
they found me.
因為戰爭打了辣麼久的緣故 可能沒有三萬塊了
Now it didn't stay 30 thousand the length of the war.
一旦激情褪去 可能就掉到八千 然後再五千了
Once passions had cold, it dropped down to eight, then five.
不過我保證 當只有五千的時候
But, I bet even when it was five thousand,
你會帶著你的幾個哥們去自首的吧
you had your share of country boys comin' to call?
你知道我會的
You know I did.
為什麼他們會懸賞你
Why did they have a reward on you?
政府因為我殺人把我財產沒收了
The Confederates took exception to my capacity for killing them.
我那時候從沃倫貝克越獄了
After I broke out of Wellenbeck,
南方政府為了侮辱我 不讓我在那繼續生活
The South took my continued existence as a personal affront.
所以法院會懸賞我
So The Cause put a reward on my head.
那個
What's...
沃倫貝克是什麼鬼
Wellenbeck?
你沒聽說過戰俘集中營 沃倫貝克
You ain't never heard of Wellenbeck prisoner of war camp, West Virginia?
我真他媽沒聽說過
No Reb, I ain't never heard of it!
你逃出來了?
You bust out?
梅爵他何止逃出來了
Maj. Marquis did more than bust out.
他想了個極屌的想法太機智
Maj. Marquis had a bright idea. So bright...
你一定好奇為什麼沒人之前想到過
you got to wonder, why nobody never thought about it before.
跟魯斯·約翰 說說你極屌的想法
Tell John Ruth about your bright idea.
整個建築都是由能著火的材料製成的
Well the whole damn place was just made out of kindling.
所以我燒了它們
So I burnt it down.
那裏都是些新手在那過夜的
There was a rookie regiment spendin' the overnight in that camp.
四十七個人燒成灰了
Forty-seven men... burnt to a crisp.
南方年輕人 農場主的兒子們
Southern youth, farmer's sons,
都是精英們我說了 燒死他們
- cream of the crop- - And I say, "Let 'em burn".
所以我應該為殺了南方的士兵而道歉
I'm suppose to apologize for killin' Johnny Reb?
你參加戰爭是為了銬著那些黑鬼
You joined the war to keep niggers in chains.
我參加戰爭是為了殺北方的白人垃圾
I joined the war to kill White Southern
意思是我可以隨便怎麼殺
Crackers And that means kill 'em anyway I can.
射他們 捅他們 淹他們 燒他們
Shoot 'em. Stab 'em. Drown 'em. Burn 'em.
朝他們頭扔大石頭
Drop a big ole' rock on their head.
隨便什麼只要能把白人垃圾打倒在地
Whatever it took to put White Southern Crackers in the ground
那就是我參加戰爭要做的事 我也這麼做了
that's what I joined the war to do, and that's what I did.
魯斯·約翰我回答你剛才問的問題
To answer your question, John Ruth,
馬庫斯 把那活的四十七個人毫無理由燒死了
when Major Marquis burned forty seven men alive,
就是為了讓他自己逃出去
for no more a reason then to give a nigger a run for the trees,
所以政府才會懸賞他
that's when The South put a reward on the head of Major Marquis.
我都把他們堆一起了 曼尼克斯
And I made them trees, Mannix.
你一定不信我經過北邊防線的時候去看了看吧
And you best belive I ain't look back till I crossed The Northern Line.
那裏有個大驚喜等你的 是吧
But you had a surprise waitin' for you on The Northern Side, didn't ya'?
一旦他們把燒死的屍體扒出來的時候
See once they started pullin' out all the burnt bodies at Wellenbeck,
發現不是所有的人都是士兵
seems not all of them boys were Rebs.
你把自己人都燒死了 是吧少校
You burnt up some of your own boys, didn't ya' Major?
他們最後一共找到多少燒死的囚犯
How many burnt prisoners they end up findin'?
是不是最後有大概37個北方人死了
Wasn't the final Yankee death count somethin' like thirty-seven?
這才是戰爭啊 曼尼克斯
That's the thing about war Mannix,
人們打仗就會死
people die.
所以你會到處說"戰爭就是地獄了"是吧
So ya' chalkin' it up to "War Is Hell", ha?
不得不承認 確實是這樣 不過如果有足夠錢的話
Well admittedly that's a hard argument to argue with. But if memory serves,
你們不會這樣想
your side didn't look at it that way.
我覺得他們會認為 三十七個白人換一個黑人
I think they thought, thirty-seven white men for one nigger
好像並不划算
wasn't so hot a trade.
我覺得他們會控告你
I belive they accused you
參加戰爭只是為了殺白人的瘋狂殺人狂
of being a kill crazy nigger who only joined the war to kill white folks
其他膚色的人對你來說就啥都不算
and the whole Blue and Grey of it all didn't really much matter to ya'.
所以他們才把你這黑鬼
And that's why they drummed your black ass outta'
在背上貼個黃條趕出騎兵團
the Cavalry with a yellow stripe down your back.
是吧 少校
Isn't it Major?
放你媽的屁
Horse shit.
要是他這麼做了 騎兵團還不一槍崩死他
If he did all that, the Cavalry woulda' shot him.
我沒說他們能證明這件事
I didn't say they could prove it.
但是他們一定能想像得出來是吧 少校
But they sure did think it out loud, didn't they Major?
但
But,
沃倫的戰鬥記錄是極好的 所以才保全了性命
Warren's war record was stellar, and that's what saved his ass.
你是不是殺了你自己的
Are you killed yourself your share of
華盛頓紅人軍隊員 是吧
redskins in your day, didn't ya' Black Major?
騎兵團可能會同情他
Cavalry tends to look kindly on that.
我來告訴你什麼是騎兵團不會同情的
I'll tell a' what The Cavalry didn't look kindly on.
就是掠奪者 曼尼克斯
Mannix's Marauders that's what.
而曼尼克斯·厄斯金的小兒子
And the fact that Erskine Mannix's little boy
在戰爭期間討論別人行為的時候
would talk about anybody else's behavior
真是讓我笑屎了..呵呵
during war time makes me wanna horse laugh.
你敢再說我爹一句!
Don't you say anything about my daddy,
他爭取的
what he fought for,
是失敗也不缺尊嚴 反對無條件的投降
was dignity in defeat, and against the unconditional surrender.
我們不是打開國門的外來入侵者
We weren't foreign barbarians pounding on the city walls.
我們曾經都是兄弟
We were your brothers.
我們應該獲得尊嚴 即使我們失敗了 只是
- We deserved dignity in defeat. - Just,
你們為了所謂的尊嚴 劫掠了多少黑人同胞的村子
how many nigger towns did y'all sack in your fight for dignity in defeat?
一樣一樣
My faire share, Black Major.
因為白人只有在黑人害怕他們的時候才能覺得安全
'Cuz when niggers are scared, that's when white folks are safe.
你再說這些仇恨黑人的話
You gonna talk that hateful nigger talk,
你到上面跟馬伕待著去
you ride up top wtih O.B.
不不不 是你們要聊政治的
No no no, you got me talkin' politics
我也不想啊
I didn't wanna'.
我跟你們說了我只是覺得活著真好
Like I said y'all, I'm just happy to be alive.
我
I...
我覺得我還是乖乖看窗外
I think I'll just look out this winda'
讓這帥氣的馬車搖我入睡
let this beatuiful carriage rock me to sleep.
然後夢到自己是如此的幸運
And dream about how lucky I am.
章節三 明妮的男裝店
Chapter Three Minnie's Haberdashery
駕
Get in there.
馭
Easy.
咋的啦
What the hell's going on,
我們沒想到今晚還有別的馬車了 we weren't expecting another stage tonight
我知道 你已經有別的客人了
I can see you already got another one up in here.
我剛把馬安頓好
I just got through putting the horses away.
這不是我們的原定路線 我們只是被暴風雪整得只能走別的道了
This ain't the normal line. But we are stuck on the wrong side of a blizzard,
看上去你要和我們一起困在這了 明妮和戴夫 在裏面不
so it looks like you're stuck with us. Are Minnie and Sweet Dave inside?
不在我只是在他們不在的時候幫忙照看店的
They ain't here. I'm running the place while they're gone.
明妮和戴夫 在哪
Where's Minnie and Sweet Dave?
他說了他們不在這他只是來這裏幫忙照看店的
He says they ain't here. He's lookin' after the place while they gone.
你是誰
Who are you?
鮑伯
I'm Bob.
好吧我管你是誰 幫 O.B.安頓馬去
Well whoever you are, help O.B. with the horses.
在暴風雪來之前 得把馬安排到暖和地方去
Get 'em outta this cold, before that blizzard hit's 'em.
我剛把其他馬整完 你要是想快點 你也得來幫忙
I just put those other horses away. You need it done fast, you need to help.
我還有倆哥們在車裏呢
I got two of my best men on it.
聽到沒 哥們 趕緊來幹活
You heard him freeloaders, get to work.
幹活去吧
Come on let's go!
開門 踹開就好
- Open up! - Kick it open!
啥 你倒是踹啊
- What? - Kick it open!
快關門 外面雪下這麼大
Shut that door,there's a goddamn blizzard out there!
你得把門釘住 你得把門釘住
- You gotta' nail it shut! - You have to nail it shut!
先別關 門邊有錘子和釘子
- Hold it shut! - There's a hammer and nails by the door!
你得把門釘住 門邊有錘子和釘子
You have to nail it shut! There's a hammer and nails by the door!
給我錘子 行
- Give me a hammer. - Yeah.
你得釘兩層木頭 一層的不夠牢
You need to do two pieces of wood! One ain't good enough!
兩層木頭 這東西他媽的壞了
- Two pieces of wood. - That fuckin' thing is busted!
不要就釘一層木頭
Not just one piece of wood.
給我另一塊木頭 好的
- Gimme that other piece of wood. - Yeah, allright.
給我釘子 給
- Gimme the nail. - Here.
媽的
Jesus.
這門是真廢物
That door's a son of a gun.
哪個傻逼弄壞的 是不是那個墨西哥人
Who's the idiot who broke that, that Mexican fella'?
我哩個去
Good heavens,
女的
a woman
小可憐 在外面一定凍壞了吧
out in this white hell. You must be frozen solid, poor thing.
看來明妮的房子人挺多啊
Looks like Minnie's got her a full house.
你們幾個什麼時候到的
When did you fella's arrive?
四十分鐘以前吧
About forty minutes ago.
那個角落裏的牛仔是你的馬伕
The Cowboy fella' in the corner, is that your driver?
不 他是個路人
No he's a passenger.
馬伕他出去了 他說他出去跟
The driver lit out. He said he was going to
他一個朋友過夜去了
spend the blizzard shacked up with a friend.
我去 這也太難喝了
Jesus Christ, that's awful!
我的天 那個墨西哥人是在杯子裏泡襪子了啊
Christ almighty, what that Mexican fella' do, soak his ole socks in the pot?
我也是這麼想的 只是說出來不太好
I think we all felt the same way, but were a little too polite to say something.
他才不會在意這個 哪有井水
- He don't have that problem. . Where's the well water?
那邊
Over there.
嗯..
So,
你們三個本來是不是要去"紅石"的
all three of you fellas' headed to Red Rock, when the blizzard stopped ya', huh?
對啊 我們都是坐外面那馬車來的
Yes, all three of us were on that stagecouach out there.
咖啡豆呢
Coffee beans?
那邊
Over there.
把手伸出來
Get your hand outta' there.
我們跟"紅石"的新治安官一起過來的
The new sheriff of Red Rock is traveling with us.
紅石鎮的治安官 怎麼可能
Sheriff of Red Rock, that'll be the day.
他要是他媽的治安官 那我就是猴子他叔叔
If he is a goddamn sheriff, I'm a monkey's uncle.
呵呵
Good.
那你就可以在馬廄分香蕉給你的黑人朋友了
Then you can share bananas with your nigger friend in the stable.
那
So...
"紅石"的新治安官跟你們一起咯
the new sheriff of Red Rock is traveling with you?
他騙人的
No he's lyin'
他才不是什麼治安官
he ain't sheriff of nothin'
他是南方的叛軍 說他自己要凍死了 就這樣
He's a southern renegade. He's just talkin' his self outta' freezin' to death, is all.
我他媽的不是跟你說了 嗯
What the fuck I tell you about talkin', huh?
我不介意在他們面前給你嘴上來一拳的
I'll bust you in the mouth right in front of these people, I don't give a fuck!
你還沒說你的名字呢
You never gave your name, sir.
魯斯·約翰
John Ruth.
你是個執法官 我正帶她去接受法律制裁呢
- Are you a lawman? - I'm takin' her to the law.
你是個賞金獵人 對啊 臭傢伙
- You're a bounty hunter? - That's right, Buster.
那你有執法證不 廢話 肯定有
- Do you have a warrant? - 'Course I do.
我能看看不
May I see it?
咋了
Why?
你應該根據程序來執行啊 我要怎麼才知道
You're suppose to produce it upon request. How am I suppose to know,
你不是壞人
you're not a villain,
沒有執法證然後綁架了這個女的
kidnapping this woman without a warrant in your possession?
你叫什麼名字 臭傢伙
What's your name, Buster?
嗯
Well...
反正不是叫 巴斯特
it certainly isn't Buster.
莫博瑞·奧斯瓦爾多
It's Oswaldo Mobray.
奧斯瓦爾多 嘿嘿
- Oswaldo? - Yes.
好吧
Well...
給你看我的執法證 奧斯瓦爾多
I got my warrant, Oswaldo.
我猜你是 多茉歌·黛西 吧 就是她
- I take it you're Daisy Domergue? - Yeah it's her.
上面寫著不論生死 對啊
- It says here, Dead or Alive? - Yeah it does.
運送像她這樣歇斯底里的囚犯
Transporting a desperate hostile prisoner such as her
應該是挺累的活吧 如果她死了
sounds like hard work. Wouldn't transporting her be easier
是不是運送起來會更方便一點
if she were dead?
沒人說這活是那麼容易干的
No one said the job was suppose to be easy.
那為什麼她完好地被吊死對你來說這麼重要
And why is her hanging proper, so important to you?
我只是想給絞刑官有點錢賺而已
Let's just say I don't like to cheat the hangman. He's gotta' make a living too.
我很欣賞你這麼做
Well I appreciate that.
讓我好好介紹一下自己
Allow me to properly introduce myself.
我是莫博瑞·奧斯瓦爾多
I'm Oswaldo Mobray,
這片地區的絞刑官
The Hangman in these parts.
那我是給你帶來生意了咯看來是的
- Looks like I brought you a customer. - So it would appear.
你有沒有曾經跟你的刑犯銬在一起超過兩天
Have you ever spent two days or more locked up with one of your customers?
並沒有噢
No I can't say I have.
別和我的囚犯說話 只有我能 懂了沒
Don't talk to my prisoner. I talk to my prisoner, that's it. You got it?
明白明白 灰常好
I got I got. Jolly good.
這還有除了咖啡以外的東西能取暖的麼
You got anything in here besides coffee that can help warm us up?
酒吧開著呢 跟我來
The Bar is open, follow moi.
好了
All right.
快點 我他媽的冷
Come on, goddamnit I'm cold!
我會給馬吃喝的你進去拿點熱咖啡吧
I'll feed and water the horses. You go inside and get some hot coffee.
我準備了些燉菜 應該快好了
I've got some stew cooking. Should be done soon.
聽著
Now look...
不管暴風雪下多大
now matter how bad this blizzard gets,
我們還是得給馬餵吃喝的 還得讓它們蹲著歇會
we still gotta' feed these horses and take a squat from time to time.
所以我和克裏斯最好能安排在一排
So me an' Chris better lay out a line
從馬廝到前門 或者從前門到茅房
from the stable to the front door, and from the front door to the shithouse.
行不行
Okay?
好主意
Good idea.
來吧 克裏斯
Come on, Chris.
我來幫你一把
I'll give you a hand.
不不不 進去吧 暖和點
No no no, go inside, get warm.
你下這麼大暴雪還在做這種髒活 我來幫你你都不要
You're doing stable work in a goddamn blizzard, I offer to help and you say no?
你說得對 哥們
You're right, mi amigo.
謝啦
Muchas gracias.
行了 跟我來
All right, follow me.
從這到前門
We gonna' drop one, every ten paces.
我們得每十步扔一個好的
- From here to the door. - Yeah! - All right.
你現在因為謀殺被通緝了
Now, you're wanted for murder.
我只是打個比方 假設你真的殺人了
For the sake of my analogy, let's just assume that you did it.
魯斯·約翰想抓你去紅石鎮接受制裁
John Ruth wants to take you back to Red Rock to stand trail for murder.
如果 你被認定有罪
And, if... you're found guilty,
紅石鎮的人民會把你吊死在廣場上 而作為絞刑者的我
the people of Red Rock will hang you in the town square. And as the hangman,
我將給你執行絞刑
I will perform the execution.
如果所有的事最終都發生了
And if all those things end up taking place,
這就是文明社會的"正義"吧
that's what civilized society calls "justice".
然而
However,
如果被你所殺的人的親屬或者愛人
if the relatives and the loved ones of the person
現在就在門口
you murdered were outside that door right now.
他們破門而入 然後拖你出去
And after busting down that door, they drug you out
把你脖子吊起來
in the snow and hung you up by the neck, that,
我們就是邊境裁決者了
we would be frontier justice.
關於邊境裁決者 好的一方面是
Now the good part
它確實快速有效
about frontier justice is it's very thirst quenching.
不過壞的方面是 它容易顛倒是非
The bad part is it's apt to be Wrong as Right.
不是說你你是活該的
Not in your case. In your case, you'd have it
但對別人來說 情況就不同了
comin'. But other people, maybe not so much.
那最終這兩種方法到底有什麼區別
But ultimately what's the real difference between the two?
真正的區別是 對於絞刑者的我來說
The real difference is Me... The Hangman.
我才不在乎你做了什麼 當我絞死你的時候
To me, it dosen't matter what you did. When I hang you, I
我不會暗爽 這只是我的工作
will get no satisfaction from your death. It's my job.
我在紅石鎮絞死你 然後我搬到別的鎮子上 我又去絞死別人
I hang you in red Rock, I move on to the next town, I hang someone else there.
那個拉動操縱桿絞死你的男人
The man who pulls the lever,
他是個公正的人
that breaks your neck will be a dispassionate man.
那份公正才是正義的精髓
And that dispassion is the very essence of
正義若是不公平地傳遞下去的話
justice. For justice delivered without dispassion,
是會危害正義本身的
is always in danger of not being justice.
阿門
Amen.
無意冒犯 牛仔大兄弟 只是想吸引一下你注意力
No offense cowboy fella', just gettin' your attention.
好吧
Yeah, well...
我注意到你了
you got it.
哥們你寫啥呢
What'cha writing firend?
唯一一個我有資格寫的東西 是啥
- Only thing I'm qualified to write about. - What's that?
我的人生傳記
My life story.
你在寫你的人生傳記 是啊
- You're writing your life story? - You bet I am.
那我被寫進去沒
Am I in it?
你才剛進來沒多久
You just entered.
既然你這麼喜歡寫東西
Well you like writing stories so much, why don't
你不如跟我說說你是怎麼來這裏的
you tell me the story that brings you here?
誰要求的 我啊
- Who's askin'? - I am.
魯斯·約翰 我帶這個女的去紅石鎮絞刑
John Ruth. I'm bringin' in this one to Red Rock to hang.
我絕不會在不知道你們是誰的情況下
Ain't no way I'm spendin' a coupla' nights under a
跟你們待在同間屋子裏
roof with somebody I don't know who you they are.
而且我還不知道你是誰 所以
And I don't know who you are. So...
你是誰
who are you?
蓋奇·喬 啥
- Joe Gage. - What?
我名字就叫 蓋奇·喬
That's my name, Joe Gage.
好吧 蓋奇·喬 你為啥要去紅石鎮
Okay Joe Gage, why you goin' to Red Rock?
我才不去紅石鎮 那你去哪
- I ain't goin' to Red Rock. - Where you goin'?
去紅石鎮外九公里的地方那是哪
- About nine miles outside of Red Rock. - What's there?
我媽那
My mother.
你媽
Your mother?
我就只是個牛仔
Listen, I'm just a cow puncher I just...
我剛長途跋涉過來
I got back from a long drive and...
這次我不止是個坐馬鞍上的牛仔
I wasn't just an ass in a saddle this time,
人生中第一次
I was a partner.
我成了生意合夥人
For the first time in my life I,
還賺了大錢
made a pretty penny and, eh....
想回家跟媽媽過聖誕節
Come home and spend time with my mother for Christmas.
哈哈哈你逗我啊
Now that's funny.
你看上去不像是會回家過聖誕節的那種人
'Cuz you don't look like the coming home for Christmas type.
呵呵
Yeah, well...
人不可貌相
you know, looks can be deceiving.
因為帥氣如我
Because I definitely am a...
就是那個回家跟媽媽過聖誕節的乖寶寶
coming home for Christmas to spend time with mother type.
跟媽媽過聖誕節
Christmas with Mother? I mean...
明明是多麼美好的一件事
it's a wonderful thing.
現在你可滿意了吧
Now is that... good enough for you?
魯斯·約翰
John Ruth?
暫時吧
For now.
只要離我犯人遠點就好
Just steer clear of my prisoner.
你好啊 老人家
Hello old timer.
將軍
General.
你
You sir,
就是個鬣狗
are a Hyena.
我並不想跟你說話
And I have no wish to speak to you.
我被叫得更難聽過
I've been called worse.
那好吧 將軍
Fair enough, General.
打擾了
Sorry to bother you.
你得踹開它 踹開
- You gonna' kick it open. - Kick it open.
這裏面已經夠冷了
It's already cold enough in here.
這沒門閂 你得拿錘子釘木板
It dosen't have latch you gonna' hammer up a board.
你得把門釘住
You gotta' nail it shut!
錘子和釘子在門邊 那邊有錘子和釘子
- The hammer and nails is by the door. - There is a hammer and nails right there!
我的天
Oh god,
克裏斯 拿一下這裏這裏
- Holdin' this Chris. - Here, here.
你得釘進去才行
You need to nail it in!
你得拿兩塊木板 把另一塊也釘進去
You need two pieces of wood. You gotta' hammer another one.
一塊不夠牢 等下就吹開了
One ain't good enough! It's gonna' blow right open.
媽蛋你要是不釘住門就得開
- Goddamn it! - It's gotta' open if you don't.
閉嘴 知道了 你媽的
- Shut up! - I got it! Son of a bitch!
我的天 這門真難伺候
Jesis Christ, that door's a whore!
我算是明白了 男裝店
I get it, haberdashery,
原來是逗我的
that was a joke.
咖啡怎麼樣
How's the coffy?
在我看來 挺棒的
Now, pretty good, if I do say so myself.
謝啦
Thank you.
猜猜他是誰
Guess who he is?
比爾·布法羅
Buffalo Bill?
才不是
Hardly, no.
我是莫博瑞·奧斯瓦爾多 我是 他是紅石鎮的絞刑官
- I'm Oswaldo Mobray, I'm The- - He's the hangman of Red Rock.
真的 是的就是我
- Oh, you are? - Yes I am.
幸會幸會 你是
Well good to meet you Mr.?
莫博瑞莫博瑞我是曼尼克斯·克裏斯
- Mobray. - Mobray, I'm Chris Mannix,
紅石鎮的新治安官真的
- the new sheriff in Red Rock. - Really?
放你媽的屁
Horseshit!
別聽他的放你媽的屁
- Pay no attention to him. - Horseshit!
那個在火爐邊取暖的哥們是我的馬伕O.B.
Fella' warmin' himself by the that pot by the stove is a hell of driver named O.B.
這是你說的唯一一件真事
That's the only thing you said that's the truth.
你去紅石鎮給勞森·蘭斯絞刑
You comin' into Red Rock to hang Lance Lawson?
確實是的
Precisely.
你有執行單不 在我包裏
- Do you have the execution orders on you? - In my beg.
我能看看不 當然行
- May I see 'em? - Of course.
誰是勞森·蘭斯
Who's Lance Lawson?
他在紅石鎮監獄已經待了快一個月了
He's a fell' been sittin' in the Red Rock jail about a month now.
他就是射殺了之前那個治安官的人
He's the fella - who shot the fella' - who was sheriff 'fore me.
說對了
Precisely.
她到底什麼意思
What did she mean when she said,
她說那個賞金獵人在馬廝裏有個黑人朋友
bounty hunter's nigger friend in the stable?
在馬廝裏 就是有個他的黑人朋友 也是個賞金獵人
He's got a nigger bounty hunter firend in the stable.
就只是為了看住她
But all that just to guard her?
我覺得他們剛開始並不是這麼想的 但
I don't think that was the original idea, but...
他們現在達成共識了
that's the idea now.
想要加點酒不 行
- Want a lil' snakebite in your coffy? - Yeah.
你們有五個人
Five of you?
喔噢 看來明妮的男裝店在接下來的幾天
Well, well, well, looks like Minnie's Haberdashery
會過得比較溫馨了
is about to get cozy for the next few days.
確實
Yes it does.
哪個小伙子有林肯的信啊
Who's the chap with the Lincoln letter?
林肯的啥
The Lincoln what?
亞伯拉罕·林肯寫的信
The letter from Abraham Lincoln
亞伯拉罕·林肯總統
President Abraham Lincoln?
你是不是他筆友 和總統
- Weren't you pen pals? - With the President?
不好意思 我聽說你們一夥人中有人有封林肯寫的信
I'm sorry, I heard somebody in your party had a
我以為是你呢
letter from Abraham Lincoln, I assumed it was you.
不是他
Not him!
是那個在馬廝裏的黑人
The black fella' in the stable.
那個馬廝裏的黑鬼有林肯寫的信
The nigger in the stable has a letter from Abraham Lincoln?
是啊
Yeah.
那個馬廝裏的黑鬼有林肯寫的信
The nigger in the stable has a letter from Abraham Lincoln?
你再說遍你叫啥
Say your name was again?
鮑伯沃倫
- Bob. - Warren.
明妮和戴夫 在麼
Minnie and Sweet Dave in there?
明妮和戴夫去山的北邊見她媽媽去了
Minnie and Sweet Dave went to visit her mother on the north side of the mountain.
什麼 是啊
- What? - Yeah.
他們不在 對啊 找媽媽去了
- They ain't here? - Yes, they're visiting her mother.
她媽媽 是啊
- Her mother? - Yes.
我沒聽明妮說過她有個媽媽啊
I never knew Minnie had a mother.
誰都有個媽媽
Everybody's got a mother.
我覺得也是
Yeah, I suppose.
她讓你管理這 是啊
- And she left you in charge? - Si.
這聽上去不像明妮的風格啊
That sure don't sound like Minnie.
你的意思是我是個騙子
Are you callin' me a liar?
沒有沒有
Not yet, I ain't.
只是聽上去有點奇怪什麼聽上去奇怪了
- But it sounds peculiar, though, - What sound peculiar?
首先 在我看來 明妮不是那種多愁善感的人
Well first of, Minnie never struck me as the sentimental type.
然後
Secondly,
我想像不出 戴夫 能拖著他肥胖的身軀
I can't imagine Sweet Dave liftin' his fat ass
去辣麼遠取井水
outta' his chair long enough to fetch well water,
除非在去北邊的路上
unless Minnie was layin' a fryin' pan upside his head.
明妮在他頭上吊了個煎餅
Along takin' trips to the north side.
我的黑人朋友 你說得好像我是個騙子咯
That sounds a whole lot like you're calling me a liar, mi negro amigo.
確實有點 是吧
Yeah it do sound a whole lot like, don't it?
但我還沒下定論噢
But I still haven't done it yet.
明妮還提供食物麼
Minnie still serve food?
你會吃燉的麼 會 那我們會提供食物的
- Do you consider stew food? - Yes. - Then we serve food.
她還在吸她的"老鵪鶉"煙斗不
She still stinkin' up the place with her "Old Quail" pipe tobacco?
明妮不吸煙斗
Minnie dosen't smoke a pipe.
她自己捲煙草
She rolls her own.
"紅蘋果煙草"
"Red Apple Tobacco"
黑人朋友 我覺得你是知道的吧
But mi negro amigo, I think you already know this.
我是知道老鮑伯
Yeah I do, Senor Bob.
只是看看你知不知道
Just seein' if you do.
給我來電O.B. 好的
- Fill me up, O.B. - Yeah.
他媽的
Goddamn it!
謝啦
Thank you.
我的天 把我腿砍了 叫我矮子好了
Well cut my legs off and call me Shorty...
這是史密瑟斯·桑福德將軍麼
is that Genaral Sanford Smithers I see?
你眼力不錯噢少年
You've got a good eye son.
哇 那我更加方了 媽蛋
Well, I'll be double dogged damned!
史密瑟斯·"看破紅塵"·桑福德
General Sandy "Don't give a damn" Smithers!
曼尼克斯掠奪者--曼尼克斯·克裏斯上尉
Captain Chris Mannix, Mannix Marauders.
厄斯金的兒子 是的
- Erskine's boy? - Yes sir.
我能坐下麼
May I sit down, Sir?
按北軍慣例的話 你隨意
According to the Yankees, it's a free country.
史密瑟斯·桑福德將軍
Genaral Sandy Smithers...
騷年啊
boy...
騷年
oh boy.
我父親真的提起過您
Did my daddy talk about you.
我聽說你把那些軟蛋們都干翻了
I heard you gave those Blue Bellies sweet hell.
我和我的軍隊們只是做了份內的事
Me and my boys did our part.
就跟厄斯金和他的軍隊一樣 干了應該做的事
Just like Erskine and his boys did their part.
確實是
Hell yeah, we did.
北軍那些狗雜種們 我從沒見過你父親誒 年輕人
- Yankees sons of bitches? - I never knew your father, son.
但我一直很敬佩他的決心
But, I always respected his resolve.
謝謝你能這麼說 將軍 你的敬意對他來說很重要
Thank you for saying that, General. Your respect woulda' meant the world to him.
我能給你拿點咖啡麼
Can I get ya' some coffy?
太棒了來杯濃的
- That would be nice. - Well, how about a blanked?
再好不過了
That would be even nicer.
這樣吧 我給你這個
Hell, you know what, you can have mine.
拿去吧 將軍
Here we go General.
不介意的話 我能問下你怎麼走懷俄明州道出來了
So what brings you out Wyoming way, sir? If ya' don't mind me askin'?
我兒子
My boy.
你還有個兒子住在紅石鎮
You gotta' boy that lives in Red Rock?
我兒子 史密瑟斯·查爾斯·切斯特
My son, Chester Charles Smithers,
他幾年前在這邊死了
he died out here a few years back.
抱歉
Forgive me sir.
不需要道歉 孩子
No forgiveness needed, son.
我說了 都是幾年前的事了
Like I said, it was a few years back.
他服完兵役之後
It was after he served his service.
他來到懷俄明山這裏
He came out here to the hills of Wyoming,
賺錢來了
to make his fortune.
再也沒收到過消息
Never to be heard from again.
我在紅石鎮公墓給他
I bought him a symbolic plot
弄了個象徵性的地方
in the Red Rock cemetery.
我來是為了找人做他的墓碑的
I'm here to advise the stone maker on his headstone.
你確定他死了
Was he a goner fer' sure?
會不會他在樹林裏正凍著呢
No chance he could be livin' "the cold life" out in
雖然是挺慘烈的 但人還能堅持吧
the woods? It's a rough life, but folks can learn it.
如果他來這做完了該做的事
If he had done what he came here to do,
他就會回家的
he'd a come home.
關上 快關上
Close it, close it!
我釘的時候 你得幫我頂著門
You have to hold it closed while I nail it shut!
什麼 那個蠢逼弄壞了門
Really? Who's the idiot who broke the damn door?
低點頂就好了
Fucking hold it low.
好了
Okay.
頂著些 黑人朋友
Hold it, mi negro amigo.
我們需要兩塊木板
We need two pieces of wood.
媽辣個雞
Ola mi cabron.
去你媽的
There you go, motherfucker!
這有好多帽子啊老鮑伯 什麼
- That's a lotta' hats, Senor Bob? - Huh?
明妮的屋內不可戴帽規矩 是吧
Considering Minnie's no hats indoors policy? Which,
如果我沒記錯 這可是這的不變規矩
If I remember it correctly, that was one of them Bar of Iron rules,
她不在的時候 估計她也想你們保持的吧
kinda rule, she'd want kept up in her absence.
看來你對帽子的要求不是很高啊
You seem to have a laissez faire attitude when it comes to the hats.
我的錯
I'm guilty.
我對帽子的規矩確實不太在意
I have a laissez faire attitude about the hats.
不如我們今天就不要管這些了
How about we forget about the hats today,
外面還下著暴雪呢
considering there's a blizzard going on and all,
然後明天才是"無帽日"怎麼樣
and make tomorrow "No Hat Day"?
好一條大黑狗
A large black dog.
拉布拉多
Labrador.
你知道我爹的 我是說
You know my daddy, I said that my daddy!
我爹總是說戴維斯是個勇氣可嘉的人
Always said that Davis was a courages man.
但他應該把軍隊放在蒙哥馬利而不是裏士滿
But he should have put capital in Montgomery and not Richmond.
是的 我同意應該把弗吉尼亞州北部的軍隊移到
Yes, Sir. I agree with that the army in North Virginia would've been used in a...
我的意思是弗吉尼亞州北部的軍隊應該以完全不同的方式安排
I said the army of North Virginia would have been used in very different way.
閉嘴
Shut up!
O.B.
O.B.?
先生 你認識那個黑人不
Do you know that nigger, Sir?
我不認識
I don't know that nigger.
我就知道他是個黑人
But I know he's a nigger.
我知道這麼多就夠了
And that's all I need to know.
那黑人可不是一般黑人
Well that nigger just ain't any nigger.
他是 史密瑟斯·桑福德將軍
- That nigger is- - General Sanford Smithers?
巴吞魯日的戰役
Battle of Baton Rouge?
告訴那個穿騎兵團制服的黑人
Inform the nigger in the Cavalry officers uniform
我手底下可有政府的組織
that I had a division of Confederates under my commend,
在巴吞魯日 你說個蛋
in Baton Rouge.
黑人大兄弟 史密瑟斯·桑福德將軍讓我告訴你 我聽到了鄉巴佬
Major Nigger, General Smithers wishes me to inform you... I heard 'em hillbilly.
告訴那老頭我曾經也在巴吞魯日
Inform this old cracker that I was in Baton Rouge also.
只不過是相反勢力
On the other side.
這下有勁了
Oh that's interesting.
史密瑟斯將軍 他說他曾經也在巴吞魯日
General Smithers, he said that he was also in Baton Rouge.
另一派.. 曼尼克斯上校 告訴那個黑人
- On the other- - Cap't Mannix, tell the nigger,
我不承認穿北方制服的黑人的地位
that I don't acknowledge niggers in Northern uniforms.
你那次抓了一大幫黑人領導者去集中營
You captured a whole Colored Command that day.
唯獨少了一個黑人騎兵 是吧
But not one Colored Trooper made it to a camp, did they?
我們既沒時間也沒食物了
We had neither the time or the food.
更沒想照顧那些北方人的馬
Nor the inclination to care for Northern horses,
還有那些北方的黑人們
and least of all Northern niggers.
所以我就地射殺了他們 夥計們
- So we shot 'em where they stood. - Gentlemen,
大兄弟
Gentlemen,
我知道美國人民不會因為
I know Americans aren't apt
無條件投降就妨礙了一場戰爭
to let a little thing like an unconditional surrender get in the way of a good war.
但我強烈建議 咱們別在暴雪中的明妮男裝店裏
But I strongly suggest we don't restage The Battle of Baton Rouge,
重新上演巴吞魯日的戰役吧
during a blizzard in Minnie's Haberdashery.
好了 黑人夥計
Now, my Nubian friend,
我覺得你有點情緒雞凍過久了
while I realize passions are high, that was a while ago.
如果你開槍殺死這個沒武器的老年人
And if you shoot this un-armed old man I guarantee
我保證等我們一到紅石鎮
I will hang you by the neck until you are dead.
我會把你吊死的
Once we arrive in Red Rock.
我他媽也保證會這麼干
I damn will guarantee that too.
是的沃倫 你跟老年人就是不能正面剛
Yeah Warren, that's the problem with old men.
你可以把他們從樓梯上踹下來 然後說
You can kick 'em down the stairs and say it's
這是意外 但你不能開槍殺他們
a accident, but ya' can't just shoot 'em.
夥計們我們被困在這
Gentlemen, since we may be trapped here,
感覺都快過去好幾天了
close together like for a few days,
我能提個合理的建議不
may I suggest a possible solution?
我們可以一分為二
We divide Minnie's in half.
北方的 和 南方的
The Northern side and The Southern Side.
把餐桌當做
With the dinner table
中立領土
operating as a neutral territory.
我們可以把那邊的火爐
We could say that the fireplace side of the room,
看作是喬治亞州的
acts as a symbolic representative of...
象徵性代表物
Georgia
那邊的吧檯 代表
While the bar, represents...
費拉德爾菲亞（費城）
Philadelphia!
只要吧檯是費城 我就無所謂了
As long as the bar's Philadelphia I agree.
我們在馬車上說的話還算數吧
We still got that deal we talked about in the wagon?
我幫你保護你的八千 你幫我保護我的一萬 說話算話 you help me protect my ten?yeah I suppose
I help you protect your eight thousand,
他們其中一個傢伙肯定說假話了
One of them fella's is not what he says he is.
那他是幹嘛的
What is he?
他肯定是這個女的同夥
He's in cahoots with this one that's what he is.
其中之一 也許其中兩個 是來救多茉歌出去的
One of them, maybe even two of 'em, is here to see Domergue goes free.
為了那個目的 他們會殺了我們所有人
And to accomplish that goal, they'll kill everbody in here.
他們還有好幾天時間 所以他們必然會
And they got 'em coupla' days. So all they gotta' do
耐心等待時機出現
is sit tight and wait for a winda' of opportunity.
然後主動出擊
And that's when they strike,
是不是 婊子?
huh bitch?
你說是就是 約翰
If you say so, John.
你確定自己沒有太多疑了嘛
Are you sure you're not just being paranoid?
我們最好的情況就是
Our best bet is this,
那個騙人的傢伙不像黛西這麼冷靜和耐心
duplicitous fella' ain't as cool a customer as Daisy here.
他不會花太多時間守株待兔
He won't have the leather patience it takes to just sit here and wait.
但是坐在這等著好的時機出現並不是那麼簡單的事
But waiting for an oportunity, and knowing it's the right one, isn't so easy.
如果他控制不住 他就會耐不住性子
If he can't handle it, he'll stop waiting.
他會自己創造時機 然後就會顯露無疑了
He'll try and create his opportunity. And that's when Mr.Jumpy reveals himself.
對這猜測你有什麼想解釋的
And what do you got to say about all this?
我有什麼想說的 關於魯斯·約翰的胡言亂語
What do I got to say? About John Ruth's ravings?
他絕對是對的
He's absolutely right.
我和其中一個傢伙是同夥
Me and one of them fella's is in cahoots. And
我們只是在等大家睡著
we're just waitin' for everybody go to sleep.
然後殺了所有人
That's when we gonna' kill y'all.
好了大家
Okay everybody,
聽我說
hear this.
這邊這位是多茉歌·黛西
This here is Daisy Domergue.
她因為謀殺被通緝了 無論死活都有
She's wanted dead or alive for murder.
一萬美元
Ten thousand dollars.
那錢已經被我收入囊中了 夥計們
That money's mine boys.
別想搶
Don't wanna' share it.
我不會失手的
I ain't gonna' lose it.
太陽出來之後 我就帶這個女人去紅石鎮絞刑
When the sun comes out, I'm taking this woman into Red Rock, to hang.
現在
Now...
在座各位
is there anybody here...
有沒有人要
comitted to stopping me`...
阻止我的
from doing that?
真的
Really?
沒人有意見咯
Nobody gotta' problem with this?
看來我是幸運的
Well, I guess that's very fortunate for me.
然而 我希望你們能理解
However, I hope you all understand,
我只是不太相信你們說的
I can't just take your word.
環境使然 我必須採取
Circumstances force me to, take...
預防措施
precautions.
你說預防措施
When you say precautions...
我怎麼感覺在針對我說呢
why do I feel you mean me?
因為我要拿走你的錢 少年 真的 是啊
- Because I'm gonna' take your gun, son. - You are? - Yes I am.
不是針對你 就拿走我的槍
- Nothing personal. - Just mine?
那個絞刑官就能有槍?
The Hangman got himself a gun too?
等收完你的 我會去收走他的
I'll be dealing with his gun after I deal with yours.
沒了錢 感覺跟裸體一樣沒安全感
I feel kinda' naked without it.
我這不還有槍嘛
Oh, I still got mine.
我會保護你的
I'll protect you.
就是幹得這麼絕是吧 約翰·魯斯
A bastards work is never done, huh, John Ruth?
怪我咯 蓋奇·喬
That's right, Joe Gage.
好了把槍給我你要嘛
- Now gimmie the gun. - You want it?
你得過來拿
You have to come and take-
冷靜
Calm down.
把你手從槍上挪開
Take your hand away from your gun.
冷靜了就眨眼
Blink if you're calm.
眨了沒他 他眨了
- Did he blink? - He blinked.
保持冷靜的話就眨眼
Blink if your gonna' remain calm?
他眨眼了 拿走他的槍
- He blinked. - Take his pistol.
真的很抱歉 孩子
I'm real sorry about this, son.
我說過了 不是針對個人 只是為了預防措施
Like I said, nothing personal. Just a precaution.
夠卑鄙的是吧
Pretty sneaky.
恐怕你也得拿出槍來了
I'm afraid the same applies to you too, Mr.
莫博瑞先生
Mobray.
預防措施是必然的 因為生命實在太珍貴了
Precautions must be taken because life is too sweet to lose.
那那個水桶給我遞過來
Hand me that little bucket.
O.B.?
去外面的廁所
Go to the outhouse.
把這個水桶帶上 全倒進屎坑裏
Take this bucket and dump it down the shit hole.
為啥得我出去啊
Why do I gotta' go outside?
你外套都穿上了 而且我還算挺相信你的
Your jacket's already on. And I sorta kinda trust you.
少校 你先來
After you Major.
好的
Okay.
吃飯的時候我會把你解開
I'm gonna' cut you loose while we eat.
別有什麼小伎倆 我對你可不會心軟
Don't get any ideas, I ain't goin' soft on ya'.
你只要把屁股離開座位超過一英吋
You lift your ass even one inch off this seat,
我就在你喉嚨上開一槍
I'll put a bullet right in your goddamn throat.
所以 多茉歌
So Domergue,
我覺得對你而言 這暴風雪就算是一種幸運吧
I suppose this blizzard counts as a stroke of luck as far as you're concerned
你沒聽我抱怨過吧 確實沒
- You don't hear me complaining do ya'? - No I sure don't.
奧斯瓦爾多 你覺得怎麼樣
How 'bout you Oswaldo?
什麼我覺得怎麼樣
How about me what?
嗯
Look,
我也是個為錢賣命的人 所以我不來評價
considerin' all the thing I done for money, I ain't one to judge.
不過你有沒有覺得絞死一個女人好像有點不妥
But don't you feel just the least little bad 'bout hangin' a woman?
如果你是個絞刑官 只要是他們沒能發明出女人不能開的槍
Till they invent a trigger a woman can't pull, if
你就得絞死女人
you're a hang man, you're going to hang woman.
好吧 看來我從來沒這麼想過
Well hell Ozzy, I guess I ain't never looked at it like that before.
只要他們是外面那些所謂的壞人的話
When it comes to some of them mean bastards
你只能做你本質工作 絞死他們
out there it's the only thing does the job.
你真的只需要絞死那些大混蛋 只要是大壞蛋 你就得絞死他們
You really only need to hang mean bastards. But mean bastards, you need to hang.
你他媽的臭傻逼
You goddamn son of a bitch!
我在外面差點凍死了
I almost died out there!
我絕對再也不會出去外面了
I ain't never going out in that shit ever, ever again!
你還好吧 O.B.?
You okay, O.B.?
還好
I'm fine.
等會就好了
I'll be fine.
我只想取暖
I just need to get warm.
要燉菜不O.B.?
You want some stew, O.B.?
等下吧
Stew, later.
好爽
That's nice.
那麼
So...
黑人少校你覺得怎麼樣
- how you doin', black Major?
曼尼克斯·克裏斯 我現在沒心情聽你扯蛋
I ain't in the mood, Chris Mannix. Leave me be from your horseshit.
魯斯·約翰說你有林肯寫的信
John Ruth says you gotta' a Lincoln Letter?
我說了 你個傻逼去別地玩去
I tole' you jackass to Hee-Haw somewhere else.
好吧 約翰
That's right, John.
你確實說了 是不是 是啊我說了
- You did say, didn't ya'? - Yeah I did.
那麼
So...
你有亞伯拉罕·林肯寫給你的信 是啊
- you got a letter from Abraham Lincoln? - Yes.
亞伯拉罕·林肯
The Abraham Lincoln?
是啊
Yes.
美利堅合眾國總統亞伯拉罕·林肯 of the United States
Abraham Lincoln The President
是啊美國的 對啊
- Yes. - Of America? - Yes.
以個人名義 給你寫的信 是啊
- Wrote you a letter, personally? - Yes.
個人名義 寫著"親愛的 沃倫少校" 不 寫著"親愛的 馬奎斯"
- Personally? As in: "Dear Maj. Warren"? - No. Personally as in: "Dear Marquis".
"親愛的 馬奎斯"美利堅合眾國總統亞伯拉罕·林肯寫的
"Dear Marquis" Abraham Lincoln the President of the United States of America?
是啊
Yes.
我能看看不 不行
- May I see it? - No you may not.
但根據約翰他說的你不止是
But the way John tells it, you weren't just some
一堆收到信件的人中 某個隨機的黑人士兵
random nigger soldier picked from a pile of letters.
照約翰說的
Way John tells it,
你們還有通信來往 是啊 - y'all hada' correspondence
- Yes.
照約翰說的話 你們基本上算是筆友咯
Way John tells it, y'all's practically pen pals?
對啊
Yes.
那筆友
And a pen pal's...
基本算是朋友了吧
practically a friend.
魯斯·約翰
John Ruth,
你不會真認為一個黑人
you really think a nigger drummed outta' the
黃條騎兵
Calvary with a yellow stripe down his back,
是美國總統的真實朋友吧
was practically friends with The President of The United States of America?
魯斯·約翰 我不想打擊你 但是 在明妮男裝店的人
John Ruth, I hate to be the one to break it to ya' but nobody in Minnie's Haberdashery,
沒有一個跟亞伯拉罕·林肯有過通信
had ever corresponded with Abraham Lincoln,
尤其是 那邊那個黑鬼
Least of all, that nigger there.
他說的對麼
Was all that horseshit?
確實是這樣的
Course it was.
看來他們跟我說的對
Well I guess it's true what they say about you people.
不能相信你口中說的任何一句話
You can't trust a fuckin' word that comes outta' your mouth.
怎麼了 魯斯·約翰
What's the matter, John Ruth?
傷到你感情了
I hurt your feelings?
還真傷害我感情了
As a matter of fact, you did.
我知道
I know,
我是你見過的唯一一個黑人哥們 我就替你節省點時間廢話吧
I'm the only black son of a bitch you ever met, so I'm gonna' cut you some slack.
你完全想像不到 作為一個黑人在美國的感受
But you got no idea, what it's like being a black man facin' down America.
黑人兄弟們唯一能感覺到安全的時候
The only time black folks are safe,
就是你們白人兄弟們消除警惕的時候 那封信
is when white folks is disarmed. And this letter,
對於消除你們的警惕有直接作用
had the desired effect of disarming white folks.
隨你怎麼解釋
Call it what you want,
我覺得就是骯髒該死的技倆
I call it a dirty fuckin' trick.
白人兄弟 你是不是想知道我為什麼撒謊吧
You wanna' know why I'd lie about something like that, white man?
還會讓我上馬車麼
Got me on that stagecoach, didn't it.
讓我來告訴你吧 約翰
Well I'll tell you like the lord tole' John,
亞伯拉罕·林肯的信對我是沒有用的
a letter from Abraham Lincoln wouldn't have that kinda' effect on me.
我可能會找個妓女撒泡尿上去我吐口水了
- I might let a whore piss on it. - I spit on it.
好樣的 大妹子
Good for you, sister.
尼瑪的 沃倫 別煩那個老人
Warren goddamit, you leave that old man alone!
坐下 你個傻逼我跟這個老人一起和平相處著呢
Stand down you son of a bitch, I shared a battle field with this man.
這你總不會否認吧
Or would you deny me that too?
我覺得咱們是和平的
I suppose you were there.
我能跟你坐下聊麼
May I join you?
請便
Yes you may.
媽蛋
Damn it.
那麼
So,
自從開戰爭以來過得怎麼樣
how's life since the war?
兩條腿還在
Got both my legs.
兩隻胳膊也還在
Got both my arms.
我就心滿意足了 有老婆沒
- I can't complain. - Got a woman?
去年冬天時候 發燒去世了
Fever took her, started this last winter.
她叫什麼名字
What was her name?
貝琪 來自喬治亞的姑娘
- Betsy. - Georgia girl?
來自奧古斯塔的
Augusta.
亞特蘭大來的男孩 奧古斯塔來的女孩
Atlanta boy, and a Augusta girl.
我曾經養過肯塔基州的馬
I use to raise Kentucky horses.
我帶那匹馬去了我買小馬的飼養主那
Her paw' was the owner of the breedershit where I brought of my ponies.
媽蛋
God damnit.
我賣了個好價錢
I made good deal on her.
拿了他給的錢 買了一片桃園
Took the stake he gave and bought a bunch peach orchards.
把自己安頓得挺好的
Set myself up pretty well.
比我其他兄弟幾個過得好得多了
Did a hell a lot better than my no good brothers, that's for damn sure.
你兒子幾年前來到這裏
Yeah, your boy came up here a few years back.
他對他媽媽評價挺高的
He spoke highly of his mama too.
你認識我兒子
You knew my boy?
我認識不 當然 Did I know him Yeah...
我認識
Yeah I knew 'em.
你不可能認識我兒子
You did not know my boy.
隨你便
Suit yourself.
你真認識我兒子
Didja' know my son?
我知道他哪天死的 你知道不 不知道
I know the day he died, - do you? - No.
你想不想知道你兒子哪天死的 想
You wanna know what day that was? yes.
就在他遇見我的那天
The day he met me.
他來這裏追殺一些黑人
He came up here to do a little nigger head huntin'.
那時候的賞金是五千還有權利炫耀一下
By then the reward was so, five thousand and bragging rights.
在戰爭困難期間對白人士兵來說 殺個黑人
But back then to battle hard rebs, five thousand just to cut off a niggers head,
取其首級就能拿五千塊確實是好事
now that's good money.
所以強尼爬上這座山來找點生意干
So the Johnny's climbed this mountain, lookin' for fortune.
結果並沒有找到能賺錢的活
But there was no fortune to be found.
只找到我了
All they found was me.
那些來這的傢伙都來自不同地方
All them fella's came up here sang a different tune,
當他們發現自己在黑人槍口下時
when they found themselves at the mercy of a nigger's gun,
"咱們這次就算了吧 你走你的陽關道 我走我的獨木橋"
"Let's just forget it. I go my way, you go yours"
你兒子切斯特就是這麼跟我說的
- that's your boy Chester talkin' - You a goddamn lie.
"你要是放我回家 我發誓
"If you just let me home to my family, I'll
我再也不會踏入懷俄明一步"
swear, I'll never set foot in Wyoming again."
這就是他們所謂的
That's what they all said.
跪求一線生機
Beggin' for his life.
你兒子跟我說了他整個人生經歷
Your boy told me his whole life story.
也提到你了噢 將軍
And you was in that story, General.
當我知道我抓住了那個
And when I knew me I had the son.
巴頓魯日戰役裏的殘忍的黑人殺戮者的兒子
Of The Bloody Nigger Killer of Baton Rouge...
我知道將會很有趣了 你給我他媽的閉嘴
- I knew me I was gonna' have some fun. - You shut your lyin' nigger lips up!
史密瑟斯將軍 你別聽他的 他不認識你兒子
General Smithers, don't you listen to him, he didn't know your boy!
他只是聽別人說了你來這是幹嘛的
He just heard, tell why you here is all!
我殺你兒子那天 是真的很冷
It was cold the day I killed your boy.
我不是指在懷俄明雪山上的那種冷 是比那還冷一點
And I don't mean snowy mountain in Wyoming cold. It was colder than that.
在那天
And on that cold day,
你兒子在我槍管的脅迫下
with your boy at the business end of my gun barrel...
我叫他脫衣服
I made him strip.
光著個屁股
Right down to his bare ass.
然後我叫他一直走
Then I told him to start walkin'.
一直光著屁股走了兩個小時 直到他倒下
I walked his naked ass for two hours, 'fore his cold collapsed him.
你一直都不認識我兒子吧 他不認識的
- You never even knew my boy? - No he didn't!
這個卑鄙的黑鬼只是想叫你拿起槍
He's just a sneaky nigger tryin' to getcha to go for that gun!
然後他又開始求我了
Then he commits to begging again.
只是這次不是為了回家
But this time he wasn't begging to go home.
他知道他再也回不去了 而且他也不求我放他一命
He knew he'd never see his home again. And he wasn't beggin' for his life neither.
因為他知道他已是將死之人
'Cos he knew that was long gone.
他只是想要個毛毯
All he wanted... was a blanket.
別太嚴格要求你兒子了 將軍
Now don't judge your boy too harshly, General. You
你絕沒有像你兒子那天那麼冷過
ain't never been cold as your boy was that day.
你一定好奇為什麼那麼冷的天一個男的要毛毯幹嘛
You'd be surprised what a man that cold, would do for a blanket.
想知道你兒子做了什麼嘛
Wanna know what your boy did?
我把我的黑大屌從褲子裏伸出來
I took my big, black, pecker outta' my pants.
我叫他在雪中一路爬過來
And I made him crawl through the snow on all fours over to it.
然後我一把抓住他腦後的頭髮
Then I grabbed a hand full of that black hair on the back his head...
然後把我的大黑屌塞進他的喉嚨裏
Then I stuck my big, black Johnson right down his goddamn throat.
因為嘴裏都是血所以很暖和
And it was fulla' blood, so it was warm.
那必然是很暖和滴
You bet your sweet ass it was warm.
然後史密瑟斯·查爾斯·切斯特
And Chester Charles Smithers,
盡全力的吸我暖和的大黑屌
sucked on that warm black dingus for long as he could.
是不是很有畫面感
Starting to see pictures, ain't ya'?
你的乖兒子啊
Your boy...
嘴裏含著大黑屌
black dudes dingus in his mouth.
他顫抖著 抽泣著
Him shakin', him cryin'
而我大笑著
me laughin'
他一定猜不到
and him not understandin'
不過你一定猜到了是吧 桑迪
But you understand, doncha' Sandy?
我沒給你兒子毛毯
I never did give your boy that blanket.
儘管他照我說的做了
Even after all he did, and he did everything I asked.
還是沒給他毛毯
No blanket.
那個毛毯不過是心碎的騙子給的一個承諾
That blanket was just a heart breakin' liar's promise.
就像聯邦軍給那些你所不承認的黑人騎兵們
Kinda' like those uniforms the union issued those colored troopers,
發的統一制服一樣
that you chose not to acknowledge.
你想怎麼樣 老傢伙
So what you gonna' do old man?
是不是要在接下來的兩三天
You gonna' spend the next two or three days,
無視我這個殺了你兒子的黑鬼
ignore the nigger that killed your boy,
無視我讓他遭受的痛苦?
Ignoring how I made him suffer?
無視我如何讓他
Ignoring how I made him...
舔遍我的大屌
lick, all over my Johnson?
你兒子做過的最傻的一件事
The dumbest thing your boy ever did...
就是讓我知道他是你兒子
was to let me know... he was your boy.
章節四 多茉歌有個秘密
Chapter Four Domergue's Got a Secret
我們走神了大概15分鐘之後
About fifteen minutes has passed, since we last left our characters.
蓋奇·喬 主動把史密瑟斯的屍體搬到外面去了
Joe Gag volunteered to take Smithers dead body outside.
我們都好奇誰會幫他一把
Straws we drawn to see who would help him...
O.B.去了
O.B. lost.
克裏斯 魯斯·約翰和奧斯瓦爾多
Chris, John Ruth and Oswaldo,
正在激烈討論剛才那次正當防衛的合法性
had vigorous debate about the legality of self-defense murder they just transpired.
沃倫·馬奎斯 深信自己的正當防衛是合法的
Marquis Warren who is supremely confident about the
一個人無視旁人的坐在桌子旁
legality of what just transpired, ignored them
喝著白蘭地酒
sat at a table by himself and drank brandy.
曼尼克斯·克裏斯上尉拿了死去的將軍的外套
Captain Chris Mannix dawn the dead Generals coat and
和奧斯瓦爾多一起點起了蠟燭和燈籠
joined Oswaldo in lighting the candles and lanterns.
嘿 奧茲 你真是機智
Hey Ozzy, hey you got the right idea.
咱們把這裏點亮點吧
Let's light this place up.
魯斯·約翰 守在門口 等蓋奇·喬和O.B.回來
John Ruth held the door close, waiting for Joe Gage and O.B. to return.
鮑伯抽著他的"紅蘋果"香煙
Bob enjoyed an manzana roja.
然而 多茉歌
Domergue, however,
自從魯斯·約翰把她解銬了之後就沒動過一下位置
hasn't moved from her spot at the community dinner table since John Ruth uncuffed her.
魯斯·約翰..
John Ruth...
怎麼了
Yeah?
我能彈那邊的吉他麼
Can I play that guitar over there?
我們先倒一下帶
Let's go back a bit.
你兒子 嘴裏含著黑大屌
Your boy, black dudes dingus in his mouth.
十五分鐘前 沃倫少校 在所有人面前射殺了史密瑟斯將軍
Fifteen minutes ago Major Warren shot General Smithers in front of everybody.
四十秒前 一件所有人都沒注意到的
But fourty seconds before that, something equally
要緊事發生了
as important happened, but not everybody saw it.
當沃倫少校那個黑屌
While Major Warren was captivating the crowd
和白人的嘴的故事吸引大家注意的時候
with tales of black dicks and white mouths...
某人在咖啡裏摻毒藥了
somebody... poisoned the coffy.
他照我說的做了 還是沒給他毛毯
He did everything I asked, no blanket.
唯一目睹了一切發生的人
And the only one to see 'em do it...
只有 多茉歌
was Domergue.
所以這一章會叫做
That's why this chapter is called...
多茉歌有個秘密
Domergue's Got a Secret.
魯斯·約翰
John Ruth.
怎麼了
Yeah.
我能彈那邊的吉他麼
Can I play that guitar over there?
行吧
Yeah.
你要是拿了除了吉他以外別的東西過來
You come back with anything else but a guitar.
我的槍就飢渴難耐了
My pistol plays a tune.
而你的死期將至 懂了沒
Domergues death march, you got it?
行行行 我知道了
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got it.
這就是你喜歡在馬車上唱的那首歌吧
That's the one you like to sing in the stagecoach, huh?
嗯
Yeah.
挺好聽的
It's kinda' pretty.
還有下一段不 有啊
- Got another verse to it? - Yeah I got.
繼續唱吧
Go ahead, sing it.
把吉他給我
Gimme that guitar!
音樂世界結束了
Music time's over!
轉過身去
Turn around.
別別別別別要要要要要閉嘴
- No, no, no, no, no. - Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, shut up!
約翰 等你下了地獄
When you get to hell, John.
告訴他們是黛西送你去那的
Tell 'em Daisy sent ya'.
曼尼克斯 咖啡有毒
Mannix the coffy!
我的天
Oh my god!
把槍給我
Gimme that fucking gun!
別考驗我的耐心 婊子
Don't test me, bitch.
你們每個人都把背靠在那邊的牆上
Everybody get your back sides up against that back wall over yonder.
媽的
Goddamit-
去不去由你 蓋奇·喬
Get or don't get, Joe Gage. It's up to you.
我去我去 那就快去
- I'll get. - Then get.
你也是 老鮑伯
You too, Senor Bob.
每個人都轉過去 把手放牆上
Everybody turn around and put your hands on that wall.
把雪板鞋拿下來
Move 'em down snowshoes.
每個人都聽好了別說話 照我說的做
Everybody keep your mouth shut and do like I say.
說話的 就得死
You open your mouth; you gonna' get a bullet.
動作太大 或者有奇怪的動作 你就會被我射中
You move a little sudden, a little strange; you gonna' get a bullet.
沒有警告 也不會有所遲疑 直接給你一槍
Not a warning, not a question; a bullet.
懂了沒
You got that?
讓我聽見你們說"我懂了""我懂了"
- Let me hear you say, "I got it". - "I got it".
"我懂了" "我懂了""我們都懂了"
- "I got it" - "I got it". - We have it.
曼尼克斯·克裏斯 你過來這邊
Chris Mannix, come over here on this side.
快點
Come on.
從我手槍套裏把槍拿出來
Take this gun out of my holster.
值著他們
Point it at them.
誰都別動一下一下都不行
Like I said, anybody does anything. And I mean, anything.
就殺了他
Kill 'em.
那麼
So...
你終於相信我說我是紅石鎮的治安官是真的咯
you finally decided I'm tellin' the truth 'bout bein' the sheriff of Red Rock, huh?
我不知道那個是不是真的
I don't know 'bout all that.
但我知道你不是下毒的那個
But you ain't the killer who poisoned that coffy.
因為你自己差點也喝了毒咖啡
'cos you almost drunk it your own damn self.
不過他們其中一個人下了毒
But one of 'em is.
把鑰匙給我
Gimme the key.
給我
Gimme the key!
你他媽的死黑鬼
You motherfucking black bastard!
你絕對會死在這山上 然後等你要死了 我會好好嘲笑你的
You're gonna' die on this mountain and I'm gonna' fucking laugh when you do!
我剛才說什麼了 不讓說話是不是
What I say 'bout talkin?
我是認真的
'Meant it, didn't I?
你得明白你剛殺了唯一一個
And you need to understand, you just killed the only
承諾會活著要帶你去紅石鎮的人
man here, comitted to gettin' you to Red Rock alive.
你們幾個其中之一肯定跟她串通好了
Now, one of y'all... is workin' with her.
或者其中兩個
Or two of y'all is workin' with her.
或者全都串通好了
Or all y'all is...
但是只有一個人下的毒
but only one of you poisoned the coffy.
所以這個女的到底有什麼魅力 讓一個男人這麼有膽量
So what charms this bitch got, take a man brave a blizzard,
這麼冷血地殺害別人 我覺得我是猜不透了
kill in cold blood, I'm sure I don't know.
只是魯斯·約翰 要絞死你
But John Ruth's trying to hang your woman,
所以你殺了他也行這能理解
so you kill him... okay- maybe.
但O.B.沒有要殺人
But O.B. wasn't hangin' nobody.
他絕對不會殺人的
He damn sure wouldn't.
但他卻躺那邊死透了 是吧
But he sure enough led over there dead now, though, ain't he?
就是你們這些 狗雜種弄的
He damn sure is you sons of bitches.
我們隨便誰喝了咖啡也會像他一樣了
Just like any one of us who'd drank that coffy.
我差點就喝了 媽蛋
Like me god damnit.
好了 你們幾個把手放牆上
Now those of y'all with your hands on the wall
都給我好好想像一下
don't practice in poison need to think about that.
想像你自己中毒翻滾在地
Think about how that coulda' you been you rollin' around on this floor.
想一下你旁邊站著的人 究竟哪個人需要為此負責
And about the men standin' next ta' ya' would be responsible.
我知道我最懷疑的是哪個誒 沒錯 看的就是你呢 蓋奇·喬
And I know who I got my money on. Yeah that's right Joe Gage I'm lookin' at you.
別妄下定論 克裏斯我們一步一步來推理
Not so fast Chris. We'll get there.
慢慢來
Let's slow it down.
慢慢來比較快
Let's slow it way down.
誰燒的咖啡
Who made the coffy?
他燒的
He did.
好像 是他 嗯 應該吧
- Yeah, he did, didn't he? - Yeah, he did, didn't he?
但是我懷疑的是那個燉菜
But it's the stew that's got me thinking.
你說明妮走多久了
How long you say Minnie been gone?
一個星期
A week?
是的
Si.
我媽媽已經也燉菜
See, my mama used to make stew.
無論放了什麼肉吃起來都一個味
And it always tasted the same, no matter the meat.
那時候種植園還有一個人 叫查理叔叔
And there was another fellow on the plantation, Uncle Charly.
他做的燉菜也跟媽媽的一個味
He made stew too and like my mama's.
從幫著打蛋到長成大人
I ate his stew from the time I was a whipper,
我一直吃他做的菜
to I was a full grown man.
無論放了什麼肉 吃起來都是那個味
And no matter the meat, it always tasted like Uncle Charly's stew.
雖然我已經六個月沒吃過明妮的燉菜了 可能沒有那麼準了
Now I ain't had Minnie's stew in six months, so I ain't no expert, but that,
但我確定那絕對是明妮做的菜
damn sure is Minnie's stew.
所以明妮要是去她媽媽那快一個星期了
So if Minnie's on the north side visiting her mama for a week,
她今天早上怎麼會做好這道菜了
how'd she make the stew this morning?
還有這個
And this?
這是 戴夫的凳子
This... is Sweet Dave's chair.
我都不敢相信我今天坐了他的凳子
When I sat in it earlier, I couldn't belive it.
沒人坐過戴夫的凳子
Nobody sits in Sweet Dave's chair.
這個店也許是明妮的但這個是戴夫的凳子
This may be Minnie's place, but this is damn sure,
我是確定無疑的
Sweet Dave's chair.
他要是也去了北邊
And if... he went to the north side....
我保證他會帶上這個凳子
I'm pretty goddamn sure that chair's be going with him.
凳子上有什麼
What's in the chair?
我剛也在想這個問題
Just what I thought.
他媽的有戴夫的血
Sweet Dave's goddamn blood.
那
So...
你是要說我謀殺了咯
are you actually accusing me of murder?
我是這麼推測的 老鮑伯
The way I see it, Senior Bob,
誰要是她的同夥
whoever's workin' with her,
誰就撒謊了如果是你的話
ain't who they say they is. And if it's you,
也就是說明妮和戴夫沒去她媽媽家
that means Minnie and her man ain't at her mama's.
他們一定死了 扔在外面什麼地方了
They're lyin' out back there dead somewhere.
如果是你這個英國佬撒謊了的話
Or if it's you British Man,
真正的莫博瑞·奧斯瓦爾多 一定也死在某個地方了
the real Oswaldo Mobray is lyin' in a ditch somewhere. And
然後你只是隨手拿走了他的證件
you're just an English fella' passin' off his papers.
或者按我的推測來 誰最醜誰就是兇手
Or we go by my theory, which is the ugliest guy did it.
就是你 蓋奇·喬
Which makes it you, Joe Gage.
我們來理一下思路
So I take it you've deduced the coffy was
咖啡在你殺了那個老人的時候被人下毒了
poisoned while you were murdering the old man?
嗯
Yes.
那這樣的話 我的黑人朋友 那個時候
Well, mi negro amigo, during that whole incident...
我正坐在房間那邊 彈著 "平安夜" 曲子
I was sitting on that side of the room. Playing Silent Night on the piano.
我沒說你下的毒我說的是 不是你做的那道燉菜
I didn't say you poisoned the coffy. I said you didn't make the stew.
我的推測是
My theory is...
你跟那個下毒的人是一夥的
you're working with man who poisoned the coffy.
你們倆一起殺了明妮和戴夫
And both of y'all murdered Minnie,
還有其他一些剛好路過的
and Sweet Dave and whoever else picked this bad luck
倒霉鬼們
day to visit Minnie's Haberdashery this morning.
某種程度上說 你們都打算伏擊魯斯·約翰 然後放了黛西
And at some point, y'all intended to bushwhack John Ruth and free Daisy.
但你沒指望暴風雪 也沒指望我們倆
But you didn't count on the blizzard and you didn't count on the two of us.
我就推測出這麼多了你覺得怎麼樣
That's as far as I got. How am I doin'?
你個黑鬼還真有想像力 是吧
Your a real imaginative nigger, ain't you?
那你是不是要因為你牽強的推測就要殺了我
So, do you intend to murder me based on a far fetched nigger theory?
還是你能拿出證據來
Or can you prove it, cabrone?
老鮑伯 其實一點也不牽強的
It ain't so far fetched, Senior Bob.
接下來就不止是我的推測了
And it's a little bit more then my theory.
你說你在明妮這打工多久了
How long you say you been working for Minnie's?
四個月
Four months.
要是你兩年半以前來這的話
If you would have been here two and half years ago
你就會發現 吧檯那邊以前掛了個牌子
you'd know about the sign used to hang above the bar.
明妮跟你說了沒 沒
- Minnie mentioned that to you? - No.
你知道牌子上寫的什麼麼 老鮑伯
You know what that sign said, Senior Bob?
"墨西哥人與狗不得入內"
"No dogs or Mexicans allowed"
明妮從開店開始 就一直掛著那個牌子
Minnie hung that sign up the day she opened this Habadashery.
一直掛了半年
And it hung over that Bar every day till she
然後她取下來了
took down, a little over two years ago.
你知道她幹嘛取下來了
You know why she took it down?
她允許狗進店了
She started lettin' in dogs.
明妮現在比較平易近人了 不過我確定她不喜歡墨西哥人
Now Minnie likes just about everybody, but she sure don't like Mexicans.
所以你跟我說 明妮去北方找他媽媽去了
So when you tell me, Minnie went to North side to visit her mama?
雖然我是不怎麼信 姑且就算是真的吧
Well I find that highly unlikely... but okay - maybe.
不過你跟我說 明妮把她最寶貝的
But when you tell me Minnie Mink took The Habadashery,
這個店
the most precious thing to her in the whole world,
交給你他媽的一個墨西哥人
and left it in hands of a Goddamn Mexican?
所以我在馬廝那說"這不像明妮的風格" 就是這個意思
Well that's what I meant in the barn when I said: "That sure don't sound like Minnie".
我知道你是騙人的 老鮑伯
Now I am calling you a liar, Senior Bob.
你撒謊了 就意味著
And if you lyin, which you are,
你殺了 明妮和戴夫
then you killed Minnie - and Sweet Dave.
四顆子彈biu~biu~biu~ 老鮑伯就這樣了
Four measly bulltes and there goes Senior, Bob.
不過我們還是不知道
That still don't get us no closer...
誰在咖啡裏下毒了
to which one of y'all poisoned the coffy, though.
是吧 克裏斯 的確不知道
- Does it Chris? - No it sure don't.
現在你們幾個下了毒 然後想救黛西的
Now one of y'all poisoned this coffy, to free Daisy.
如果你們幾個傻逼
If I don't hear a confession from one of you
沒人快點承認的話
motherfuckers quick, fast and in a hurry,
我就把讓那個臭女人喝了這壺毒咖啡
I'm gonna' pull this whole pot of coffy, down that bitches goddamn throat.
好了 時間到
Okay, time's up.
停停停! 好吧 是我幹的 是我下的毒
Stop! Alright I did it, it was me I poisoned the coffy.
他媽的我就知道是你
I fuckin' knew it!
你這謀殺犯 你要狗帶了
You gonna' die now you murderin' bastard.
沃倫少校 讓我親手送這個狗蛋東西去死吧
Major Warren please let me sent this ugly son of a bitch to hell.
你殺了O.B.十個你都不如他 沃倫我現在能開槍了沒
You killed O.B. he's worth ten of you! Warren can I kill him?
跟你的蛋蛋說再見吧
Say adios to your Huevos.
沃倫少校
Major Warren?
我可沒槍啊 治安官
I ain't got no gun, sheriff.
章節五四個路人
Chapter Five The Four Passengers
這天早上
Earlier That Morning.
你好啊 查理 你過得怎麼樣 你好啊 艾迪 朱迪
- Hey Charly my, how the hell are you? - Hi ya' Ed, hi ya' Judy-
你今天帶了幾個人 滿座了都
- How many ya' got? - Full house today, friend.
你們進去等等吧
We got on in there waiting.
那他得等等了 我們這可沒地方坐了
Well he's gonna' hafta keep on waitin' cause we ain't got no room.
這你得跟明妮說
Well you need to tell Minnie. Cause he's been
他都來了兩天了 明妮不想他再待這了
here two days and Minnie wants him outta here.
可我也沒座了 不能怪我
Well I can't give him a seat I don't have -
你把那幾個路人們帶進去 讓明妮認識
Listen why don't you take the passengers inside, introduce them to Minnie.
喝點咖啡取取暖 好的
- Warm youself up and drink some coffy. - Okay.
咱們終於到了 明妮男裝店
Here we are everybody, Minnie's Haberdashery.
你們覺得好了
Step outside you and your friends can stretch
就進來
your legs. When you're reday, stop on inside,
喝點咖啡 還有火能取暖 我會帶你們去見明妮的
get warm by the fire, get some coffy in you. I'll introduve you to Minnie.
嗨 明妮
Hi Minnie!
我不想多嘴你的生意之道
I'm not trying to tell you how to run your business.
只是我覺得咖啡怎麼也得先準備好吧
But I would think coffy would be the first thing you'd make.
過來吧你們 別害羞	帽子都摘了
- Come on in everybody, don't be shy. - Hats!
這是明妮 這是她的房子
Everybody, this is Minnie, and this is her place.
我後面那個抓雞毛的是 吉瑪
Behind me pluckin' that chicken is Gemma.
吉瑪笑得是真歡
Lovley smile, that Gemma.
那個穿制服的人我不認識
Now the fella' in the uniform I don't know but
不過跟他下棋的人 是戴夫
the one he's playing chess with is Sweet Dave.
你好啊 戴夫你好 朱迪
- Hi ya' Dave. - Hey Judy.
明妮 給你介紹這幾個客人
And Minnie, these are the passengers.
這還不夠好噢
Well that's not good enough.
把面罩拿開 讓我看看你們 說下你們名字吧
Go take away them rags, let's see some faces let's hear some names.
莫博瑞·奧斯瓦爾多 女士
Oswaldo Mobray, madame.
蓋奇·喬
Joe Gage.
鮑伯
Bob.
喬迪
And I'm Jody.
在這麼冷的鬼地方還能發現一個
It's a pleasant surprise to find such a warm
這麼溫暖的避難處真是夠驚喜的
sanctuary in the middle of such a cold hell.
你們請隨意去壁爐邊取取暖吧
Well make yourself comfortable. Get warm by the fire.
不了 我們幾個在那個火爐那取暖就夠了 行不行
We're just gonna' go warm ourself's by the stove, if that's all right?
火爐 還是壁爐 隨便你們 只要能暖和
Stove, fireplace, whatever. Just get warm.
聽朱迪說這有世界上最好喝的咖啡
Oh, and Judy said something about the best coffy in the world?
我確實也聽見朱迪說了 世界上最好喝的咖啡
Yes I do belive Judy did say something about the best coffy in the world.
哈哈哈 這我可不能保證 不過我告訴你們
Well I don't know 'bout all that. But I'll tell ya what it is.
咖啡又熱又濃又好喝
It's hot and it's strong and it's good. And
在這種大雪天 你們一定會爽翻的
in this snow it sure 'nuff warms your ass up.
明妮你別就說說 你倒是做去啊
You don't need to sell it, Minnie, you need make it.
你給我下來
And you need to get your ass out there and
幫查理去拿行李 還有扶艾迪進來
help Charly with them bags and get Ed in here.
遵命 但咖啡得弄好啊我不得先弄死你
- Yes, ma'am, but fix the coffy. - I'll fix you!
我不認識 一個老人家
I don't know some old man.
我都不知道咱們該怎麼辦了
Well I don't know what I'm suppose to do about it.
我知道複述一下她說的
I'm just tellin' you what she said.
她只是叫我出來幫查理的她想跟你說話
Anyway she sent me out here to help Charly, she wants to talk to you.
交給我了 艾迪
Got 'em, Ed.
明妮女士 你能給我卷跟煙麼
Miss Minnie? Would you roll me a cigarette?
沒問題 我抽的是紅蘋果牌煙草 會抽不
Sure honey, I smoke Red Apple Tobacco, that all right?
我的最愛
It's my favorite.
別管我你們我就看看不說話
Don't mind me gentlemen, I'm just watching.
你會下棋不
You play?
嗯..我大概有過至少十二個個人教我下棋了
You know, I must of had at least twelve people,
我就是記不住怎麼下
teach me that goddamn game. Just never could keep the moves in my head.
要是沒打擾你們的話 我能看看麼
But if I'm not disturbing, I like to watch?
沒打擾 我喜歡在別人面前殺崩這個老傢伙
Hell no. I like whippin' this old man's ass in front of a audience,
殺崩你粑粑
You ain't whippin' shit.
非常感謝 我的女士
Merci beaucoup Mademoiselle, Minnie.
哇 太酷了 你說的是什麼 法語
- Oh that's real nice, what is that? - It's french.
你會說法語 是的
- You speak french? - Oui-
oui 什麼意思 意思是 對的
- Oui - what is that mean? - It means yes.
oui 對的
Oui - Yes.
戴夫 你快問我屁股大不大 啥
- Hey Dave, ask me if my ass is fat. - What?
問我 我的屁股大不大 大啊
- Ask me if my ass is fat? - It is.
我讓你問我 憑啥
- I said ask me! - Why?
問就好了 你屁股大不大
- Just do it! - Is your ass fat?
oui你看 我也能說法語了
Oui, look at that y'all I can speak French.
你這裏有糖賣麼
Are you the jelly bean salesman around here?
5分錢我能買幾根薄荷棒
How many peppermint sticks I get for a nickel?
五根
Five.
好的
All right.
給 謝啦
- Here. - Thank you sugar.
來了
Okay.
我來幫你 女士
Allow me to assist you, madame.
我幫你們把行李拿過來了
I brought in your bags in case anybody wants
以防萬一有人想換換衣服
to change your clothes before Red Rock.
要薄荷棒不
Peppermint stick?
謝啦
Thanks.
他們為啥都叫你 六馬朱迪
So why do they call you Six Horse Judy anyway?
哈哈因為我是你們見過唯一能同時騎六匹馬的朱迪啊
Cause I'm the only Judy you've ever seen that could drive a six horse team?
呵呵 我居然問這麼傻的問題
Hell yeah, kinda of a stupid question.
你能幫我扶下梯子不 放心 堅如磐石 穩得很
- Could you holding this for me? - Rock steady, madame. Rock steady.
你口語好好聽 你是哪裏人 英國的
You gotta' very sweet accent, where that from, England?
我可不這麼覺得 新西蘭
- I take exception to that! - New Zeeland.
小心點 女士 是不是在舊西蘭邊上
- Carefull, madame. - Is it anywhere near Old Zealand?
奧克蘭 奧克蘭是哪
Auckland, what the fuck is an Auckland?
我就是那裏來的那是我們那最大的城市了呢
It's where I'm from, it's our biggest city.
咖啡好了 終於他媽的好了
- Coffy's ready! - It's about damn time.
山裏最好喝的咖啡出爐了你真會開玩笑
- Best coffy on the mountain. - I'll don't know 'bout all that.
馬伕喜歡喝路人就不一定喜歡了
Stagecoach drivers like it. Passengers, not so much.
可能會有點濃
Most find it a mite too strong.
剛剛好啦 謝啦
Can't be too strong on this mountain, thank you.
你覺得怎麼樣
Well, what'd ya' think?
我去
Shit!
他還算有點用 雖然沒什麼用 還是有點的
He adds something, not much, but something.
你覺得呢 皮特
What do you think, Pete?
不得不說 好像對我們的埋伏還算有點迷惑作用
Well I must admit, he does make the set up more convincing.
咱們要不要把屍體都搬到門外的井裏去
Do we collect the bodies and chuck 'em in the well out there?
然後把馬解了 都帶到馬廝喂起來
And then start unhitching the horses and get 'em in the barn and get 'em fed.
等等 弄那些馬算容易的了
Well hang on, by puttin the horses away that's easy enough.
把這幾個胖子拎出去是真他媽的難
To drag these fat bastards up and down the mountain that's fucking impossible, mate.
我剛來這打工的
Look I just started working here.
不知道明妮做了什麼事惹你們了
Whatever Minnie to make y'all mad.
真的沒我什麼事
I had nothing to do with it.
老人家
Well old man,
你要是一隻貓剛才發生的事
if you was a cat what just happened here
夠讓你的九條命丟了一條了
would count as one of your nine lives.
你知道不知道你差點就跟那些黑鬼死一起了
You realize how close you came to being tossed on a pile of niggers?
知道知道 但你絕不會因為殺了
- Yes. And when it comes to that pile of niggers we building out back,
外面那些死掉的黑鬼就成將軍的是吧
won't take nothin' to make you General of it. You believe that?
我覺得也是別著急 老人家
- I expect no less. - Not so fast old man.
你還有機會活著出去的
You might have a way out of this yet.
今天晚些時候
Later today,
有個不要命的大兄弟要過來這裏
dirty son of a gun's gonna come in here.
我妹妹也跟他一起
And he's gonna have my sister with him,
他把我妹妹用鐵鏈銬住了
and he's gonna have her in chains.
要帶去紅石鎮絞死
He's taking her into Red Rock to be hung.
你知道為啥不 不知道
- You know why? - No.
就因為
Ten thousand dollars.
一萬塊
That's why.
等他們到了
And when he get's here.
我就殺了那傢伙 然後放了我妹妹
I'm gonna' kill that fella' and turn my sister lose.
你有沒有想阻止我
Now do you have any reason why you'd want to interfere
把我妹妹從那個人那救出來的衝動
with me saving my sister from a hangman's rope?
毫無沒有是吧
- No. - You don't.
真沒有 確定沒有咯
- No I don't. - You sure you don't.
我們剛殺了明妮和戴夫
I mean we did just kill Minnie and Sweet Dave.
而我看你跟戴夫關繫好像還挺好的
You and Sweet Dave seemed pretty chummy over here.
我也是剛認識這些人我他媽才不管他們 還有你和你妹妹
I just met these people. I don't give a damn about them, or you, or your sister,
還是其他懷俄明的狗雜種呢
or any other son of a bitch in Wyoming for that matter.
非常好 老人家
That is a good answer, old man.
等他們來了
So when they get here,
你就只管坐那就好了啥事都別干
you just sit your ass in this chair. And you don't do nothin'.
啥話也別說 就說說 你好 謝謝 晚安 就夠了
You don't say nothin'. Hello, thank you, good night, that's about it.
說自己名字也行 不能再多了
Maybe your name, but that's it.
你好 謝謝 晚安 還有
Hello, thank you, good night and...
你的名字 噢 我的名字
- Maybe your name. - Maybe my name.
就當個傻子一樣的老人乖乖睡覺去就好了
Be an old man, be dotty. Go to sleep.
絕對不要跟那個抓了我妹妹的賞金獵人
And don't you say nothin' and I mean nothin'
說任何別的東西
to that bounty hunter that's got my sister.
明白沒 明白
- Do you understand? - Yes.
等我無傷解決了他 放了我妹妹之後 我就會讓你走
When it's safe I kill him, free my sister and leave you be.
成不
Deal?
行 謝了
Deal, thank you.
接下來的四個小時 喬迪他們幾個忙著把屍體扔進井裏
During the next four hours, Jody and the boys chuck the bodies down the well.
安置馬匹
Put away the horses.
打掃了一下店裏
Tidied around Minnie's.
藏了把槍以備後患
Stash weapons for further use.
然後等著魯斯·約翰和黛西的馬車來
And waited for John Ruth and Daisy's Stage to arrive.
來了來了
Here they come.
好了 夥計們
Okay boys, this is it
都給我準備好了
Let's get ready.
記住了 就算我們有四個人
Now remember, it dosen't matter if we have four men or fory,
魯斯·約翰 他都拿著槍
we're still gonna' be facing John Ruth chained
對著我妹妹的肚子
to my sister with a pistol pointed at her belly.
要想在他殺了我姐之前 先殺了他 可沒那麼容易
Now killin' that fella' 'fore he kills my sister, ain't gonna' be easy.
不過我們就是為了那個目標來的
But you believe that's exactly what we're gonna do.
所以我們都得有耐心
So the name of the game here is patience.
只要在困在這兩三天 他一定會閉眼睡覺的
Trapped here for two or three days, at some point, he will close his eyes
然後你們就可以一槍崩了他
and that's when you blow the top of his head off.
你給我聽好了 老人家 我姐要是不能活著出去 你也別想活著出去
Remember old man, my sister don't make it off this mountain alive, neither do you.
我會盡力的
I'll do my best.
祝你好運 哥們
Good luck, mate.
咋的啦 我們沒想到今晚還有別的馬車會來了
What the hell's going on, we weren't expecting another stage tonight?
我知道 你已經有別的客人了
I can see you already got another one up in here.
我剛把馬安頓好
I just got through putting the horses away.
這不是我們的原定路線 我們只是被暴風雪整得只能走別的道了
This ain't the normal line. But we are stuck on the wrong side of a blizzard,
看上去你要和我們一起困在這了
so it looks like you're stuck with us.
再來釘一塊
I can do another one.
明妮和戴夫 在麼
And Sweet Dave inside?
不在我只是在他們不在的時候幫忙照看店的
They ain't here. I'm running the place while they're gone.
明妮和戴夫 在哪
Where's Minnie and Sweet Dave?
他說了他們不在這他只是來這裏幫忙照看店的
He says they ain't here. He's lookin' after the place while they gone.
你是誰 鮑伯
- Who are you? - I'm Bob.
好吧我管你是誰 幫O.B.安頓馬去
Well whoever you are, help O.B. with the horses.
在暴風雪來之前 得把馬安排到暖和地方去
Get 'em outta this cold, before that blizzard hit's 'em.
我剛把其他馬整完 你要是想快點 你也得來幫忙
I just put those other horses away. You need it done fast, you need to help.
我還有倆哥們在車裏呢
I got two of my best men on it.
聽到沒 哥們 趕緊來幹活
You heard him freeloaders, get to work.
幹活去吧
Come on let's go!
開門 踹開就好 啥
- Open up! - You have to kick it open! - What?
你倒是踹啊
Kick it open!
終章 黑人 白人的地獄
Last Chapter Black Man, White Hell
老夥計 你覺得怎麼樣了
How you doin' old boy?
他們把我蛋射掉了 痛死爹了
They shot my nuts off they're freezin'
像殺豬一樣留了好多血
burining up the same time, bleedin like a stuck pig.
我覺得我快不行了
I think I'm gonna die.
都是這些狗娘養的幹的好事
And these motherfuckers did it.
你怎麼樣了
That's how I'm doin'. How you doin'?
我腿疼死了
Well my leg hurts really bad.
不過我要是把重心放在右腳的話
But I think if I'm put all my weight on my right foot-
我就是假裝關心一下 我才懶得鳥你的腿
I'm just bein' sarcastic I don't give a fuck about your leg.
你開心就好
Just make yourself comfortable.
別擔心我了 媽蛋 我屁股沒感覺了
Don't worry about my comfort. Shit! I can't feel my ass no more.
還是提防一下這幾個雜碎 還有那個在地下室的狗蛋東西
Worry about these owl hoots and that bushwhacker nuts shooter in the basement.
好的
All right!
你
You!
在地下室的傢伙
Fella' in the basement!
我數到三 你要不投降的話
You either give up by the time I count to three,
我就在多茉歌頭上來一槍
or I shoot Domergue in the head.
一 二
One!... Two!...
別別別 別殺她 我出來
No, no, no, no! Don't shoot her! I'm comin' up!
等下 你個偷襲人的狗東西
Hold on there you bushwhacker sack shooter, you
你先把通道口打開 我叫你出來再出來
just open the door we tell you to come up!
把槍扔出來
Now throw out your pistol!
朝床這邊扔
Throw it to the bed.
他肯定還有一把
Well he got another.
把另一把也扔出來
Now throw out your other pistol.
我沒槍了!
I ain't got another pistol!
你生也要給我生出來
Well you better shit another pistol out your ass!
要是你不扔出槍來 再過兩秒我就要殺了那個賤人了
Cause if you don't throw one up here in the next two seconds we gonna' kill this bitch!
你看 跟你說了有的
See? told ya'.
現在
Now...
把你手放在我能看見的地方
with your hands where we can see 'em...
慢慢地給我爬出來
slowly come on up!
笨蛋 沒事吧
How ya' doin' dummy?
看到你來了 總算是好一點了
Better.now I see your ugly face.
感覺如何 你個偷襲人的大傻屌
How you like you that? You bushwhacker castrator!
幹嘛呢你 他都投降了
What are you doin' he was giving up?
誰叫他慢吞吞的 我就解決他了
It took him too long so I done for him.
蓋奇·喬 過來把那塊木板關上
Joe Gage get your ass over and shut this trap door.
節哀吧
I'm sorry, honey.
我能坐那麼
May I sit in the chair?
行 你去吧
Yes you may.
雙手都放桌面上
Keep your hands flat on that table.
都別動
And don't move 'em.
曼尼克斯
Mannix!
這次你可站錯隊了
You sure picked the wrong time to turn into a nigger lover.
你難道還不明白 那個黑鬼和魯斯·約翰已經把你置於危險之中了嗎
Don't you see that nigger and John Ruth put you smack dab in the middle of danger?
你就要在這個明妮的房子裏死了
You're about to be murdered in some nigger named
還死的不知所以然
Minnie's house and you don't even know why!
行了 賤人
Okay, bitch...
我不信 為啥
I'll bite... why?
我跟這三個傢伙都是一夥的
I am workin with all three of them fella's...
不是因為他們喜歡我
but not cause they got butterflies in their belly 'bout me.
而是因為我們都是一個幫派的 喬迪多茉歌幫
But because we're all gang members, The Jody Domergue Gang!
你們剛殺的那個在地下室的人 是我哥哥 喬迪多茉歌
That fella' y'all just killed in the basement, was Jody Domergue, my brother!
喬迪多茉歌是他媽的誰
Well who the hell, is Jody Domergue?
你來告訴他吧 賞金獵人
You wanna tell 'em bounty man?
他可是個大頭目他值五萬塊
He's a big bad cat. He's worth fifty thousand dollars.
他們幫派的每個人都至少值一萬
And every member of his gang is wort at least ten.
難怪你會值一萬
witch finally explains why you're worth ten.
等太陽出來後
And what's gonna' happen when that sun comes
我哥那十五個弟兄們
out nigger, so is my brother's fifteen men
就會來找我們你來跟他們說
comin' straight here for us! Tell 'em Grouch!
喬迪在紅石鎮還有十五個弟兄等著
Jody's got fifteen men waitin' in Red Rock.
要是我們沒能殺掉魯斯·約翰然後救了黛西
If we couldn't kill John Ruth and free Daisy here.
他們就會殺遍鎮子 直到殺了約翰 救出黛西
Their job was to sack the town, kill John Ruth and free Daisy there.
現在我哥死了 我就是幫派的老大了是吧 弟兄們
Now with brohter dead, I'm in charge of this gang, right boys?
是是是
Oh yeah.
我跟你說克裏斯 你到現在為止還沒有做什麼特別過份的事
And Chris I'm tellin' you, you ain't done anything yet, we can't forgive.
所以
So...
我們來做個交易吧 沒得聊 賤人
- let's make a deal? - No deals, bitch!
你打算讓那個黑鬼替你說話 克裏斯
You gonna' let that nigger speak for you, Chris?
慢著 沃倫
Hold it Warren.
她好像沒啥話可說了
Seein' as she ain't got nothin' to sell, I'm
我倒是越來越好奇她還有啥好逗我的了
kinda curious about her sales pitch, humor me.
行吧 賤人
All right, bitch.
你有啥交易好做的
What's... your... deal?
慢慢來
Easy.
拿你的槍 殺了那個黑鬼
Take your gun, shoot that nigger dead.
然後相安無事地在這坐兩天
Then we sit here all nice like for the next two days.
等雪融化了
When the snow melts...
我們就回墨西哥 你就回你的紅石鎮當你的治安官
we go back to Mexico and you go on to Red Rock to get that star pinned on your chest.
我們能把馬克交給他
Well... we can give 'em Marco.
鮑伯的真名是 墨西哥馬克
Bob's real name is "Marco The Mexican".
他值一萬二美元
He's worth twelve thousand dollars.
那就是墨西哥馬克 答對了
- That's "Marco The Mexican"? - Precisely, yeah.
狗屁 我射爆他的頭之後 馬克就一塊都不值了
Shit, after I blew his face off, Marco ain't worth a peso.
要是我接下來的兩天裏死了我知道很有可能會死 你可以領走我屍體
If I die in the next two days, which is more than likely, you can have me.
英國人 黑塔古斯·皮特 我被政府懸賞
Under the name "English Pete Hicox" I've gotta' federal
一萬五美元
bounty of fifteen thousand dollars on my head.
你可以把錢都拿走 克裏斯皮特 你再廢話的話
- And it's all your Chris. - You keep talkin', Pete.
你就是自尋死路了
You gonna talk yourself to death.
蓋奇·喬你又是誰
Joe Gage, who you be?
道格拉斯·古拉奇 你聽說過他麼
- Grouch Douglass. - You heard of him?
是啊 我聽說過他他跟黛西一樣值一萬美元
Yeah, I heard of Grouch Douglass. He's worth ten, just like Daisy.
那你告訴我
Remind me,
為什麼我不能直接殺了你們幾個 然後領錢去
why we wouldn't just kill all y'all and cash in?
是啊 你完全可以殺光我們 只是你們絕對活著出不了這座山
Oh, you can kill us all. But you'll never spend a cent of that bounty money
然後花一分錢了
and you'll never leave this mountain alive.
因為雪一化 其他那些弟兄們
Because when that snow melts, the rest of Jody's
另外十五個大兄弟 都在紅石鎮等著
gang - all fifteen of 'em - that were waiting,
來這找我們
in Red Rock are comin' here.
就算你把我們都殺了
Now let, let's say you shoot us all...
你要是想領我們多茉歌幫的賞金
If you really want all that Domergue Gang bounty money,
你還得把我們屍體都帶到紅石鎮去
you still got to get all our corpses into Red Rock.
那可不容易噢 我也不信你能同時騎四匹馬的馬車
And that ain't gonna' be so easy. Cause I doubt you can drive a four horse team.
但是兩匹馬又拉不動
And that wagon out there is too heavy for a two horse team.
所以就是說 你得一人一匹馬騎著去紅石鎮
So that means you're gonna' hafta' lead a string of horses into Red Rock
外面剛下了這麼大的雪
And with that deep snow after a blizzard,
你是不可能逃得掉的 就算一人一匹馬吧
you ain't gonna' be able to get away with any more then let's say one body per horse.
你一個人 牽著四匹馬去紅石鎮
So that's you, leading a string of four horses into Red Rock,
在那麼多雪的雪地裏
and with all them horses, in that snow,
都得是你一個人 你休想走得有多快
and you all by your lonesome, you're gonna be a mite poky.
然後你會剛好落入我們幫派的手中
And you gonna' run smack dab into The Domergue
古拉奇 咱們有多少人
Gang and again Grouch, how many is that?
十五個身強力壯的殺手然後等他們
- Fifteen killer strong. - And when those fifteen killers,
遇到你的時候
come across you,
看見你帶這我們幾個的屍體
in possession of all of our dead bodies, they
他們不止會殺了你和這個黑鬼
ain't just gonna' kill you and that nigger.
他們會回紅石鎮 殺了鎮上的每個人
There gonna go back to Red Rock and kill every son of a bitch in that town.
你要真的是紅石鎮的治安官 你想不想救鎮民們
You really the Sheriff of Red Rock? You wanna save the town?
那就開槍殺了那個黑鬼
Then shoot that nigger dead!
你現在倒相信上帝了啊 賤人 很好 你很快就會去見上帝了
You belive in Jesus now, huh, bitch? Well good 'cos 'bout meet him!
還有誰 嗯
Anybody else wanna' make a deal, huh?
交易還有效 克裏斯
The deal still stands, Chris.
你還沒做什麼不可原諒的事
You ain't done we can't forgive.
主要還是那個黑鬼
It's still all on that nigger.
你殺了他 帶走我們的屍體
Shoot 'em dead, take my body
帶黛西出去 然後
and sit out the snow with Daisy and Grou-
曼尼克斯
Mannix!
把我的手槍給我
Give me my pistol!
拿過來
Catch 'em here.
那麼
So...
你剛才說 我們坐在這
you were sayin'... we sit here...
相安無事的
all nice and friendly like...
度過接下來的兩天
for the next two days...
等雪化了
then the snow melts,
你去你們幫派的兄弟匯合 然後坐火車回墨西哥
you leave here, meet up with your gang and high tail it to Mexico?
是
Yeah.
然後我能帶走奧斯瓦爾多和蓋奇·喬
And I get Oswaldo and Joe Gage?
對
Yeah.
可是喬迪值五萬 他怎麼辦
But Jody's worth fifty thousand, what 'bout his body?
你竟然要跟那個煩人的賤人達成協議
You gonna make a deal with this diabolical bitch?
我還沒說我接受了呢 我們就只是嘮嗑 冷靜點
I'm not sayin' I'm gonna' make a deal with her, we're just talkin'. Calm down.
那喬迪的屍體呢 五萬塊呢
So what about Jody's body and the fifty thousand?
你太貪了啊 那個不行
You've gotten greedy, Reb, no deal.
我們得帶走朱迪的屍體 他是有孩子的人
We take Jody's body back with us he got children.
那我只有殺了沃倫 我們就成朋友了咯
So I kill, Warren... and we're all friends?
對頭!
Yeah.
不可能 小婊砸
No deal, tramp.
克裏斯 你犯了這輩子最大的一個錯誤
Chris you're makin' the biggest mistake of your life!
等我們的弟兄們幾天以後到這裏 他們還不弄死你
When our boys get here in a coupla' days, their gonna cut your nuts off!
紅石鎮會被殺得片甲不留
And there won't be a stick left in that town unburnt.
哇 我覺得我現在是不是應該嚇尿了
Well I guess I should be plum scared right now, huh?
你要是有腦子的話 是該嚇尿了
If you had any brains, you would be.
黛西
You see...
問題是
here's the problem Daisy.
我要是真的被你的威脅嚇住了
In order for me to be scared of your threats,
那我還得信你說的還有十五個弟兄在紅石鎮等著的鬼話咯
I got to believe in those fifteen extra gang members waitin' it out in Red Rock.
呵呵 我才不信
And boy, oh boy... I sure don't.
我只知道
What I belive is...
是蓋奇·喬或者那個管他什麼鬼名字的道格拉斯
Joe Gage or Grouch Douglass whatever the fuck his name was....
給咖啡下的毒
poisoned the coffy...
然後你看到了
and you watched him do it.
你看我差點喝了 然後啥也沒說
And you watched me pork up and didn't say shit...
我才發現
and I believe...
你原來一直都是
you all what you've always been...
一個愛騙人的小婊砸
a lyin' bitch, who will do anything...
就為了騙那個要吊死你的人
to cheat that rope waitin' for her in Red Rock.
只要有必要 你願意做任何事
Including shittin' out fifteen extra gang members,
包括這十五個兄弟都是騙人的
Whenever you needs be.
還有
And...
我覺得你說的多茉歌幫派
I believe when it comes to what's left of The Jody Doe-ming-grey Gang...
就只是我現在看著的這幾個
I'm lookin' at 'em, right here right, right
在地板上死得透透的了
now. Dead on this on this motherfuckin' floor.
真TM聰明
Goddamn right.
克裏斯 你也得死在這
You're gonna' die on this mountain, Chris.
我哥可有一支幫派放屁
- My brother leds an army of men- - Horse Shit!
我爹才領導過一支軍隊 他領導的反叛軍 為了一個注定失敗的事業而戰鬥
My daddy led an army, he led a renegade amry, fightin' a lost cause!
現在我爹戰後只剩四百人在身邊了
My daddy held up to four hundred men together after the war
啥都沒了 只是他們都很敬重我爹 信得過他的指揮
with nothing but their respect in his command.
你的哥哥只是領導一群殺手的垃圾
Your brother's just a owl hoot who led a gang of killers.
我好像不太舒服
I don't feel so good.
我去
Oh, shit.
你還活著麼 小子
You still alive, white boy?
曼尼克斯
Mannix?
艸
Fuck!
小子
Hey, boy!
快起來
Get up!
曼尼克斯·克裏斯 快把屁股坐起來
Chris Mannix! Your ass ain't nailed to the floor!
快TM的醒過來
Wake the fuck up!
你倒是醒啊 小伙子
Wake up, white boy!
我還沒死呢混蛋
I ain't dead yet, you black bastard.
曼尼克斯·克裏斯 看來我之前錯怪你了
Chris Mannix, I may have misjudged you.
現在我們才到重點
Now we've come to the part of the story...
看我不崩了你的腦袋 別 先別開槍
- where I blow your goddamn head off! - No, no, no don't shoot her!
為啥不行
Why the hell not?
魯斯·約翰
John Ruth.
他這個混蛋確實是狠角色
John Ruth was one mighty, mighty bastard.
你知道他死之前
What's the last thing...
做了什麼
that bastard did, 'fore he died?
救了你一命
Was save your life.
我們都快死了 小伙子
We gonna' die, white boy.
這點我們毋庸置疑
We ain't got no say in that.
只是還有一件事我們沒確定
But there's one thing left we do have a say in.
那就是怎麼殺這個婊砸
And that how we kill this bitich.
我覺得 一槍殺了她好像對她太仁慈了點
And I say, shootin's to good for her...
魯斯·約翰 本可以隨便在路上哪裏就開槍的
John Ruth coulda shot her anywhere, anytime along the way,
但他堅持要絞刑
but John Ruth was The Hangman...
當絞刑者抓住你 你會被開槍殺死
and when The Hangman catches ya', you don't die by no bullet.
當絞刑者抓住你
When the The Hangman catches ya'...
你只會被絞死
you hang.
你只需要絞死那些大混蛋
"You only need to hang Mean Bastards."
只要是大壞蛋 你就得絞死他們
"But Mean Bastards, you need to hang".
這是我第一次也是最後一次當紅石鎮治安官
As my first and final act as the Sheriff of Red Rock,
多茉歌 我判處你
I sentence you, Domergue,
被絞刑至死
to hang by the neck until dead.
堅持住 黛西 我還想看看呢
Hang on, Daisy. I wanna watch.
看 魔鬼的步伐
Now that, was a nice dance.
真的相當完美
That sure was pretty.
嘿
Hey...
我能看看那份林肯寫的信麼
can I see that Lincoln Letter?
親愛的 馬奎斯
Dear Marquis...
我希望寫這封信時
I hope this letter finds you...
你身體無恙然後
in good health and stat...
我一切都好
I'm doing fine...
儘管我希望時間能再多一點
altough I wish there were more hours in the day....
只是工作太繁多
is just so much to do...
時間無痕
time's changing slowly... but surely...
但如你這般的男子必有所作為
and it's men like you that will make a difference...
你的軍隊不止是你的榮耀
your military success was a credit...
也是你們種族的驕傲
not only to you... but your race as well...
每當我聽到你的消息我都相當自豪
I'm very proud everytime I hear new of you...
我們還有很長的一段路要走 只要同舟共濟
we still have a long way to go, but hand in hand...
一定能實現的
I know we'll get there...
我只想讓你明白 你一直在我心中
I just want to let you know, you're in my thoughts...
共盼未來我們能相見
hopefully our paths will cross in the future...
而我還是你的朋友
until then... I remain your friend...
瑪麗來催了
ole' Mary Todd's calling...
我該睡覺去了
so I guess it must be time for bed...
亞伯拉罕·林肯 致敬
respectfully... Abraham Lincoln.
瑪麗·陶德 真是感人
Ole' Mary Todd... That's a nice touch.
是啊
Yeah... Thanks.